The B-WORK_OF_ART
Shawshank I-WORK_OF_ART
Redemption I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1994 B-DATE
American B-NORP
drama O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Frank B-PERSON
Darabont I-PERSON
based O
on O
the O
1982 B-DATE
Stephen B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
novella O
Rita B-WORK_OF_ART
Hayworth I-WORK_OF_ART
and I-WORK_OF_ART
Shawshank I-WORK_OF_ART
Redemption I-WORK_OF_ART
It O
tells O
the O
story O
of O
banker O
Andy B-PERSON
Dufresne I-PERSON
who O
is O
sentenced O
to O
life O
in O
Shawshank B-ORG
State I-ORG
Penitentiary I-ORG
for O
the O
murders O
of O
his O
wife O
and O
her O
lover O
despite O
his O
claims O
of O
innocence O
Over O
the B-DATE
following I-DATE
two I-DATE
decades I-DATE
he O
befriends O
a O
fellow O
prisoner O
contraband O
smuggler O
Ellis B-PERSON
Red I-PERSON
Redding I-PERSON
and O
becomes O
instrumental O
in O
a O
money O
laundering O
operation O
led O
by O
the O
prison O
warden O
Samuel B-PERSON
Norton I-PERSON
William I-PERSON
Sadler I-PERSON
Clancy B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
Gil B-PERSON
Bellows I-PERSON
and O
James B-PERSON
Whitmore I-PERSON
appear O
in O
supporting O
roles O
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Godfather I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1972 B-DATE
American B-NORP
crime O
film O
directed O
by O
Francis B-PERSON
Ford I-PERSON
Coppola I-PERSON
who O
co O
wrote O
the O
screenplay O
with O
Mario B-PERSON
Puzo I-PERSON
based O
on O
Puzo B-PERSON
s O
best O
selling O
1969 B-DATE
novel O
of O
the O
same O
name O
The O
film O
stars O
Marlon B-PERSON
Brando I-PERSON
Al B-PERSON
Pacino I-PERSON
James B-PERSON
Caan I-PERSON
Richard B-PERSON
Castellano I-PERSON
Robert B-PERSON
Duvall I-PERSON
Sterling B-PERSON
Hayden I-PERSON
John B-PERSON
Marley I-PERSON
Richard B-PERSON
Conte I-PERSON
and O
Diane B-PERSON
Keaton I-PERSON
It O
is O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
installment O
in O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Godfather I-WORK_OF_ART
trilogy I-WORK_OF_ART
The O
story O
spanning O
from B-DATE
1945 I-DATE
to I-DATE
1955 I-DATE
chronicles O
the O
Corleone B-PERSON
family O
under O
patriarch O
Vito B-PERSON
Corleone I-PERSON
Brando I-PERSON
focusing O
on O
the O
transformation O
of O
his O
youngest O
son O
Michael B-PERSON
Corleone I-PERSON
Pacino I-PERSON
from O
reluctant O
family O
outsider O
to O
ruthless O
mafia O
boss O
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Dark I-WORK_OF_ART
Knight I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2008 B-DATE
superhero O
film O
directed O
co O
produced O
and O
co O
written O
by O
Christopher B-PERSON
Nolan I-PERSON
Based O
on O
the O
DC B-ORG
Comics I-ORG
character O
Batman B-PERSON
the O
film O
is O
the O
second B-ORDINAL
installment O
of O
Nolan B-PERSON
s O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Dark I-WORK_OF_ART
Knight I-WORK_OF_ART
Trilogy I-WORK_OF_ART
and O
a O
sequel O
to O
2005 B-DATE
s O
Batman B-WORK_OF_ART
Begins I-WORK_OF_ART
starring O
Christian B-PERSON
Bale I-PERSON
and O
supported O
by O
Michael B-PERSON
Caine I-PERSON
Heath I-PERSON
Ledger I-PERSON
Gary B-PERSON
Oldman I-PERSON
Aaron B-PERSON
Eckhart I-PERSON
Maggie B-PERSON
Gyllenhaal I-PERSON
and O
Morgan B-PERSON
Freeman I-PERSON
In O
the O
film O
Bruce B-PERSON
Wayne I-PERSON
Batman B-PERSON
Bale I-PERSON
Police O
Lieutenant O
James B-PERSON
Gordon I-PERSON
Oldman I-PERSON
and O
District O
Attorney O
Harvey B-PERSON
Dent I-PERSON
Eckhart I-PERSON
form O
an O
alliance O
to O
dismantle O
organized O
crime O
in O
Gotham B-GPE
City I-GPE
but O
are O
menaced O
by O
an O
anarchistic O
mastermind O
known O
as O
the B-PERSON
Joker I-PERSON
Ledger I-PERSON
who O
seeks O
to O
undermine O
Batman B-PERSON
s O
influence O
and O
throw O
the O
city O
into O
chaos O
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Godfather I-WORK_OF_ART
Part I-WORK_OF_ART
II I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1974 B-DATE
American B-NORP
epic O
crime O
film O
produced O
and O
directed O
by O
Francis B-PERSON
Ford I-PERSON
Coppola I-PERSON
from O
the O
screenplay O
co O
written O
with O
Mario B-PERSON
Puzo I-PERSON
starring O
Al B-PERSON
Pacino I-PERSON
Robert B-PERSON
Duvall I-PERSON
Diane B-PERSON
Keaton I-PERSON
Robert B-PERSON
De I-PERSON
Niro I-PERSON
Talia B-PERSON
Shire I-PERSON
Morgana B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
John B-PERSON
Cazale I-PERSON
Mariana B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
and O
Lee B-PERSON
Strasberg I-PERSON
It O
is O
the O
second B-ORDINAL
installment O
in O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Godfather I-WORK_OF_ART
trilogy I-WORK_OF_ART
Partially O
based O
on O
Puzo B-PERSON
s O
1969 B-DATE
novel O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Godfather I-WORK_OF_ART
the O
film O
serves O
as O
both O
a O
sequel O
and O
a O
prequel O
to O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Godfather I-WORK_OF_ART
presenting O
parallel O
dramas O
one O
picks O
up O
the O
1958 B-DATE
story O
of O
Michael B-PERSON
Corleone I-PERSON
Pacino I-PERSON
the O
new O
Don O
of O
the O
Corleone B-PERSON
family O
protecting O
the O
family O
business O
in O
the O
aftermath O
of O
an O
attempt O
on O
his O
life O
the O
prequel O
covers O
the O
journey O
of O
his O
father O
Vito B-PERSON
Corleone I-PERSON
from O
his O
Sicilian B-NORP
childhood O
to O
the O
founding O
of O
his O
family O
enterprise O
in O
New B-GPE
York I-GPE
City I-GPE
. O

Twelve B-WORK_OF_ART
Angry I-WORK_OF_ART
Men I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
an O
American B-NORP
courtroom O
drama O
written O
by O
Reginald B-PERSON
Rose I-PERSON
concerning O
the O
jury O
of O
a O
homicide O
trial O
It O
was O
broadcast O
initially O
as O
a O
television O
play O
in O
1954 B-DATE
The B-DATE
following I-DATE
year I-DATE
it O
was O
adapted O
for O
the O
stage O
It O
was O
adapted O
for O
a O
film O
of O
the O
same O
name O
directed O
by O
Sidney B-PERSON
Lumet I-PERSON
and O
released O
in O
1957 B-DATE
Since O
then O
it O
has O
been O
given O
numerous O
remakes O
adaptations O
and O
tributes O
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Lord I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Rings I-WORK_OF_ART
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Return I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
King I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2003 B-DATE
epic O
fantasy O
adventure O
film O
directed O
by O
Peter B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
based O
on O
the O
third B-ORDINAL
volume O
of O
J B-PERSON
R I-PERSON
R I-PERSON
Tolkien I-PERSON
s O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Lord I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Rings I-WORK_OF_ART
The O
film O
is O
the O
final O
entry O
in O
the O
Lord O
of O
the O
Rings O
trilogy O
and O
was O
produced O
by O
Barrie B-PERSON
M I-PERSON
Osborne I-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
and O
Fran B-PERSON
Walsh I-PERSON
from O
a O
screenplay O
by O
Walsh B-PERSON
Philippa B-PERSON
Boyens I-PERSON
and O
Jackson B-PERSON
Continuing O
the O
plot O
of O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Two I-WORK_OF_ART
Towers I-WORK_OF_ART
Frodo B-PERSON
Sam I-PERSON
and O
Gollum B-PERSON
are O
making O
their O
final O
way O
toward O
Mount O
Doom O
in O
Mordor O
in O
order O
to O
destroy O
the O
One O
Ring O
unaware O
of O
Gollum O
s O
true O
intentions O
while O
Gandalf O
Aragorn O
Legolas O
Gimli O
and O
the O
rest O
are O
joining O
forces O
together O
against O
Sauron O
and O
his O
legions O
in O
Minas O
Tirith O
It O
was O
preceded O
by O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Fellowship I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Ring I-WORK_OF_ART
2001 B-DATE
and O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Two I-WORK_OF_ART
Towers I-WORK_OF_ART
2002 I-WORK_OF_ART
. O

Pulp B-WORK_OF_ART
Fiction I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1994 B-DATE
American B-NORP
black O
comedy O
crime O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Quentin B-PERSON
Tarantino I-PERSON
who O
conceived O
it O
with O
Roger B-PERSON
Avary I-PERSON
Starring O
John B-PERSON
Travolta I-PERSON
Samuel B-PERSON
L I-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
Bruce B-PERSON
Willis I-PERSON
Tim B-PERSON
Roth I-PERSON
Ving B-PERSON
Rhames I-PERSON
and O
Uma B-PERSON
Thurman I-PERSON
it O
tells O
several O
stories O
of O
crime O
in O
Los B-GPE
Angeles I-GPE
The O
title O
refers O
to O
the O
pulp O
magazines O
and O
hardboiled O
crime O
novels O
popular O
during O
the B-DATE
mid I-DATE
20th I-DATE
century I-DATE
known O
for O
their O
graphic O
violence O
and O
punchy O
dialogue O
. O

Schindler B-WORK_OF_ART
s I-WORK_OF_ART
List I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1993 B-DATE
American B-NORP
historical O
drama O
film O
directed O
and O
produced O
by O
Steven B-PERSON
Spielberg I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
Steven B-PERSON
Zaillian I-PERSON
It O
is O
based O
on O
the O
1982 B-DATE
non O
fiction O
novel O
Schindler B-WORK_OF_ART
s I-WORK_OF_ART
Ark I-WORK_OF_ART
by O
Australian B-NORP
novelist O
Thomas B-PERSON
Keneally I-PERSON
The O
film O
follows O
Oskar B-PERSON
Schindler I-PERSON
a O
German B-NORP
industrialist O
who O
saved O
more B-CARDINAL
than I-CARDINAL
a I-CARDINAL
thousand I-CARDINAL
mostly O
Polish B-NORP
Jewish B-NORP
refugees O
from O
the O
Holocaust B-EVENT
by O
employing O
them O
in O
his O
factories O
during O
World B-EVENT
War I-EVENT
II I-EVENT
It O
stars O
Liam B-PERSON
Neeson I-PERSON
as O
Schindler B-PERSON
Ralph B-PERSON
Fiennes I-PERSON
as O
SS B-ORG
officer O
Amon B-PERSON
G I-PERSON
th O
and O
Ben B-PERSON
Kingsley I-PERSON
as O
Schindler B-PERSON
s O
Jewish B-NORP
accountant O
Itzhak B-PERSON
Stern I-PERSON
. O

Fight B-WORK_OF_ART
Club I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1999 B-DATE
American B-NORP
film O
directed O
by O
David B-PERSON
Fincher I-PERSON
and O
starring O
Brad B-PERSON
Pitt I-PERSON
Edward B-PERSON
Norton I-PERSON
and O
Helena B-PERSON
Bonham I-PERSON
Carter I-PERSON
It O
is O
based O
on O
the O
1996 B-DATE
novel O
of O
the O
same O
name O
by O
Chuck B-PERSON
Palahniuk I-PERSON
Norton B-PERSON
plays O
the O
unnamed O
narrator O
who O
is O
discontented O
with O
his O
white O
collar O
job O
He O
forms O
a O
fight O
club O
with O
soap O
salesman O
Tyler B-PERSON
Durden I-PERSON
Pitt I-PERSON
and O
becomes O
embroiled O
in O
a O
relationship O
with O
a O
destitute O
woman O
Marla B-PERSON
Singer I-PERSON
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Lord I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Rings I-WORK_OF_ART
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Fellowship I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Ring I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2001 B-DATE
epic O
fantasy O
adventure O
film O
directed O
by O
Peter B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
based O
on O
the O
1954 B-DATE
novel O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Fellowship I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Ring I-WORK_OF_ART
the O
first B-ORDINAL
volume O
of O
J B-PERSON
R I-PERSON
R I-PERSON
Tolkien I-PERSON
s O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Lord I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Rings I-WORK_OF_ART
The O
film O
is O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
installment O
in O
the O
Lord O
of O
the O
Rings O
trilogy O
It O
was O
produced O
by O
Barrie B-PERSON
M I-PERSON
Osborne I-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
Fran B-PERSON
Walsh I-PERSON
and O
Tim B-PERSON
Sanders I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
Walsh B-PERSON
Philippa B-PERSON
Boyens I-PERSON
and O
Jackson B-PERSON
The O
film O
features O
an O
ensemble O
cast O
including O
Elijah B-PERSON
Wood I-PERSON
Ian B-PERSON
McKellen I-PERSON
Liv B-PERSON
Tyler I-PERSON
Viggo B-PERSON
Mortensen I-PERSON
Sean B-PERSON
Astin I-PERSON
Cate B-PERSON
Blanchett I-PERSON
John B-PERSON
Rhys I-PERSON
Davies I-PERSON
Billy B-PERSON
Boyd I-PERSON
Dominic B-PERSON
Monaghan I-PERSON
Orlando B-PERSON
Bloom I-PERSON
Christopher B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
Hugo B-PERSON
Weaving I-PERSON
Sean B-PERSON
Bean I-PERSON
Ian B-PERSON
Holm I-PERSON
and O
Andy B-PERSON
Serkis I-PERSON
It O
was O
followed O
in O
2002 B-DATE
by O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Two I-WORK_OF_ART
Towers I-WORK_OF_ART
and O
in O
2003 B-DATE
by O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Return I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
King I-WORK_OF_ART
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Good I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Bad I-WORK_OF_ART
and I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Ugly I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1966 B-DATE
Italian B-NORP
epic O
spaghetti O
Western O
film O
directed O
by O
Sergio B-PERSON
Leone I-PERSON
and O
starring O
Clint B-PERSON
Eastwood I-PERSON
as O
the O
Good O
Lee B-PERSON
Van I-PERSON
Cleef I-PERSON
as O
the O
Bad O
and O
Eli B-PERSON
Wallach I-PERSON
as O
the O
Ugly O
Its O
screenplay O
was O
written O
by O
Age O
Scarpelli B-PERSON
Luciano B-PERSON
Vincenzoni I-PERSON
and O
Leone B-PERSON
based O
on O
a O
story O
by O
Vincenzoni B-PERSON
and O
Leone B-PERSON
Director O
of O
photography O
Tonino B-PERSON
Delli I-PERSON
Colli I-PERSON
was O
responsible O
for O
the O
film O
s O
sweeping O
widescreen O
cinematography O
and O
Ennio B-PERSON
Morricone I-PERSON
composed O
the O
film O
s O
score O
including O
its O
main O
theme O
It O
was O
an O
Italian B-NORP
led O
production O
with O
co O
producers O
in O
Spain B-GPE
West B-GPE
Germany I-GPE
and O
the B-GPE
United I-GPE
States I-GPE
Most O
of O
the O
filming O
took O
place O
in O
Spain B-GPE
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Lord I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Rings I-WORK_OF_ART
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Two I-WORK_OF_ART
Towers I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2002 B-DATE
epic O
fantasy O
adventure O
film O
directed O
by O
Peter B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
based O
on O
the O
second B-ORDINAL
volume O
of O
J B-PERSON
R I-PERSON
R I-PERSON
Tolkien I-PERSON
s I-PERSON
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Lord I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Rings I-WORK_OF_ART
The O
film O
is O
the O
second B-ORDINAL
instalment O
in O
the O
Lord O
of O
the O
Rings O
trilogy O
and O
was O
produced O
by O
Barrie B-PERSON
M I-PERSON
Osborne I-PERSON
Fran B-PERSON
Walsh I-PERSON
and O
Jackson B-PERSON
from O
a O
screenplay O
by O
Walsh B-PERSON
Philippa B-PERSON
Boyens I-PERSON
Stephen B-PERSON
Sinclair I-PERSON
and O
Jackson B-PERSON
The O
film O
features O
an O
ensemble O
cast O
including O
Elijah B-PERSON
Wood I-PERSON
Ian B-PERSON
McKellen I-PERSON
Liv B-PERSON
Tyler I-PERSON
Viggo B-PERSON
Mortensen I-PERSON
Sean B-PERSON
Astin I-PERSON
Cate B-PERSON
Blanchett I-PERSON
John B-PERSON
Rhys I-PERSON
Davies I-PERSON
Bernard B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
Christopher B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
Billy B-PERSON
Boyd I-PERSON
Dominic B-PERSON
Monaghan I-PERSON
Orlando B-PERSON
Bloom I-PERSON
Hugo B-PERSON
Weaving I-PERSON
Miranda B-PERSON
Otto I-PERSON
David B-PERSON
Wenham I-PERSON
Brad B-PERSON
Dourif I-PERSON
Karl B-PERSON
Urban I-PERSON
and O
Andy B-PERSON
Serkis I-PERSON
It O
was O
preceded O
by O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Fellowship I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Ring I-WORK_OF_ART
2001 B-DATE
and O
followed O
by O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Return I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
King I-WORK_OF_ART
2003 B-DATE
. O

The O
Matrix B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1999 B-DATE
science O
fiction O
action O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
the O
Wachowskis B-PERSON
It O
is O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
installment O
in O
The O
Matrix B-WORK_OF_ART
film O
series O
starring O
Keanu B-PERSON
Reeves I-PERSON
Laurence B-PERSON
Fishburne I-PERSON
Carrie B-PERSON
Anne I-PERSON
Moss I-PERSON
Hugo B-PERSON
Weaving I-PERSON
and O
Joe B-PERSON
Pantoliano I-PERSON
It O
depicts O
a O
dystopian O
future O
in O
which O
humanity O
is O
unknowingly O
trapped O
inside O
a O
simulated O
reality O
the O
Matrix O
which O
intelligent O
machines O
have O
created O
to O
distract O
humans O
while O
using O
their O
bodies O
as O
an O
energy O
source O
When O
computer O
programmer O
Thomas B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
under O
the O
hacker O
alias O
Neo B-PERSON
uncovers O
the O
truth O
he O
joins O
a O
rebellion O
against O
the O
machines O
along O
with O
other O
people O
who O
have O
been O
freed O
from O
the O
Matrix B-WORK_OF_ART
. O

Goodfellas B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1990 B-DATE
American B-NORP
biographical O
crime O
drama O
film O
directed O
by O
Martin B-PERSON
Scorsese I-PERSON
written O
by O
Nicholas B-PERSON
Pileggi I-PERSON
and O
Scorsese B-PERSON
and O
produced O
by O
Irwin B-PERSON
Winkler I-PERSON
It O
is O
a O
film O
adaptation O
of O
the O
1985 B-DATE
nonfiction O
book O
Wiseguy B-WORK_OF_ART
by O
Pileggi B-PERSON
Starring O
Robert B-PERSON
De I-PERSON
Niro I-PERSON
Ray B-PERSON
Liotta I-PERSON
Joe B-PERSON
Pesci I-PERSON
Lorraine B-PERSON
Bracco I-PERSON
and O
Paul B-PERSON
Sorvino I-PERSON
the O
film O
narrates O
the O
rise O
and O
fall O
of O
mob O
associate O
Henry B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
and O
his O
friends O
and O
family O
from B-DATE
1955 I-DATE
to I-DATE
1980 I-DATE
. O

One B-CARDINAL
Flew B-WORK_OF_ART
Over I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Cuckoo I-WORK_OF_ART
s I-WORK_OF_ART
Nest I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1975 B-DATE
American B-NORP
psychological O
comedy O
drama O
film O
directed O
by O
Milo B-PERSON
Forman I-PERSON
based O
on O
the O
1962 B-DATE
novel O
of O
the O
same O
name O
by O
Ken B-PERSON
Kesey I-PERSON
The O
film O
stars O
Jack B-PERSON
Nicholson I-PERSON
as O
Randle B-PERSON
McMurphy I-PERSON
a O
new O
patient O
at O
a O
mental O
institution O
and O
features O
a O
supporting O
cast O
of O
Louise B-PERSON
Fletcher I-PERSON
Will I-PERSON
Sampson I-PERSON
Danny B-PERSON
DeVito I-PERSON
Sydney B-PERSON
Lassick I-PERSON
William B-PERSON
Redfield I-PERSON
as O
well O
as O
Christopher B-PERSON
Lloyd I-PERSON
and O
Brad B-PERSON
Dourif I-PERSON
in O
their O
film O
debuts O
. O

Hamilton B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2020 B-DATE
American B-NORP
historical O
fiction O
musical O
drama O
film O
consisting O
of O
a O
live O
stage O
recording O
of O
the O
2015 B-DATE
Broadway B-FAC
musical O
of O
the O
same O
name O
which O
was O
inspired O
by O
the O
2004 B-DATE
biography O
Alexander B-WORK_OF_ART
Hamilton I-WORK_OF_ART
by O
Ron B-PERSON
Chernow I-PERSON
It O
was O
directed O
and O
produced O
by O
Thomas B-PERSON
Kail I-PERSON
and O
produced O
written O
and O
composed O
by O
Lin B-PERSON
Manuel I-PERSON
Miranda I-PERSON
Miranda B-PERSON
also O
stars O
as O
Treasury B-ORG
Secretary O
and O
Founding O
Father O
Alexander B-PERSON
Hamilton I-PERSON
along O
with O
the O
musical O
s O
original O
principal O
Broadway B-ORG
cast O
. O

Parasite B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2019 B-DATE
South B-NORP
Korean I-NORP
black O
comedy O
thriller O
film O
directed O
by O
Bong B-PERSON
Joon I-PERSON
ho I-PERSON
who O
co O
wrote O
the O
screenplay O
with O
Han B-PERSON
Jin I-PERSON
won O
The O
film O
starring O
Song B-PERSON
Kang I-PERSON
ho I-PERSON
Lee O
Sun O
kyun O
Cho O
Yeo O
jeong O
Choi O
Woo O
shik O
Park B-PERSON
So I-PERSON
dam I-PERSON
Jang B-PERSON
Hye I-PERSON
jin I-PERSON
and O
Lee B-PERSON
Jung I-PERSON
eun I-PERSON
follows O
a O
poor O
family O
who O
scheme O
to O
become O
employed O
by O
a O
wealthy O
family O
and O
infiltrate O
their O
household O
by O
posing O
as O
unrelated O
highly O
qualified O
individuals O
. O

Soorarai B-WORK_OF_ART
Pottru I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2020 B-DATE
Indian B-NORP
Tamil B-LANGUAGE
language O
drama O
film O
directed O
by O
Sudha B-PERSON
Kongara I-PERSON
and O
produced O
by O
Suriya B-PERSON
and O
Guneet B-PERSON
Monga I-PERSON
under O
their O
respective O
banners O
2D B-ORG
Entertainment I-ORG
and O
Sikhya B-ORG
Entertainment I-ORG
The O
story O
was O
conceptualised O
and O
written O
by O
Kongara B-PERSON
The O
screenplay O
was O
written O
by O
Kongara B-PERSON
and O
Shalini B-PERSON
Ushadevi I-PERSON
with O
an O
additional O
screenplay O
by O
Aalif B-PERSON
Surti I-PERSON
and O
Ganesha B-PERSON
and O
Vijay B-PERSON
Kumar I-PERSON
writing O
the O
dialogue O
The O
film O
stars O
Suriya B-PERSON
Aparna I-PERSON
Balamurali I-PERSON
and O
Paresh B-PERSON
Rawal I-PERSON
with O
Mohan B-PERSON
Babu I-PERSON
Urvashi I-PERSON
and O
Karunas B-PERSON
amongst O
others O
in O
supporting O
roles O
. O

Interstellar B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2014 B-DATE
epic O
science O
fiction O
film O
co O
written O
directed O
and O
produced O
by O
Christopher B-PERSON
Nolan I-PERSON
It O
stars O
Matthew B-PERSON
McConaughey I-PERSON
Anne B-PERSON
Hathaway I-PERSON
Jessica B-PERSON
Chastain I-PERSON
Bill B-PERSON
Irwin I-PERSON
Ellen B-PERSON
Burstyn I-PERSON
Matt B-PERSON
Damon I-PERSON
and O
Michael B-PERSON
Caine I-PERSON
Set O
in O
a O
dystopian O
future O
where O
humanity O
is O
struggling O
to O
survive O
the O
film O
follows O
a O
group O
of O
astronauts O
who O
travel O
through O
a O
wormhole O
near O
Saturn B-LOC
in O
search O
of O
a O
new O
home O
for O
mankind O
. O

City B-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
God I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2002 B-DATE
Brazilian B-NORP
epic O
crime O
film O
co O
directed O
by O
Fernando B-PERSON
Meirelles I-PERSON
and O
Kátia B-PERSON
Lund I-PERSON
released O
Brazil B-GPE
in O
2002 B-DATE
and O
worldwide O
in O
2003 B-DATE
Bráulio B-PERSON
Mantovani I-PERSON
adapted O
the O
story O
from O
the O
1997 B-DATE
novel O
of O
the O
same O
name O
written O
by O
Paulo B-PERSON
Lins I-PERSON
but O
the O
plot O
is O
loosely O
based O
on O
real O
events O
It O
depicts O
the O
growth O
of O
organized O
crime O
in O
the O
Cidade B-GPE
de I-GPE
Deus I-GPE
suburb O
of O
Rio B-GPE
de I-GPE
Janeiro I-GPE
between B-DATE
the I-DATE
end I-DATE
of I-DATE
the I-DATE
1960s I-DATE
and O
the O
beginning O
of O
the O
1980s O
with O
the O
film O
s O
closure O
depicting O
the O
war O
between O
the O
drug O
dealer O
Li B-PERSON
l I-PERSON
Zé I-PERSON
and O
vigilante O
turned O
criminal O
Knockout B-PERSON
Ned I-PERSON
The O
tagline O
is O
If O
you O
run O
the O
beast O
catches O
you O
if O
you O
stay O
the O
beast O
eats O
you O
. O

Spirited B-WORK_OF_ART
Away I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2001 B-DATE
Japanese B-NORP
animated O
fantasy O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Hayao B-PERSON
Miyazaki I-PERSON
animated O
by O
Studio B-ORG
Ghibli I-ORG
for O
Tokuma B-ORG
Shoten I-ORG
Nippon I-ORG
Television I-ORG
Network I-ORG
Dentsu B-ORG
Buena I-ORG
Vista I-ORG
Home I-ORG
Entertainment I-ORG
Tohokushinsha B-ORG
Film I-ORG
and O
Mitsubishi B-ORG
and O
distributed O
by O
Toho B-ORG
The O
film O
features O
the O
voices O
of O
Rumi B-PERSON
Hiiragi I-PERSON
Miyu B-PERSON
Irino I-PERSON
Mari I-PERSON
Natsuki B-PERSON
Takeshi B-PERSON
Naito I-PERSON
Yasuko B-PERSON
Sawaguchi I-PERSON
Tsunehiko B-PERSON
Kamijō I-PERSON
Takehiko B-PERSON
Ono I-PERSON
and O
Bunta B-PERSON
Sugawara I-PERSON
Spirited B-WORK_OF_ART
Away I-WORK_OF_ART
tells O
the O
story O
of O
Chihiro B-PERSON
Ogino I-PERSON
Hiiragi I-PERSON
a O
ten B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
girl O
who O
while O
moving O
to O
a O
new O
neighborhood O
enters O
the O
world O
of O
Kami B-PERSON
After O
her O
parents O
are O
turned O
into O
pigs O
by O
the O
witch O
Yubaba B-PERSON
Natsuki B-PERSON
Chihiro I-PERSON
takes O
a O
job O
working O
in O
Yubaba B-PERSON
s O
bathhouse O
to O
find O
a O
way O
to O
free O
herself O
and O
her O
parents O
and O
return O
to O
the O
human O
world O
. O

Saving B-WORK_OF_ART
Private I-WORK_OF_ART
Ryan I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1998 B-DATE
American B-NORP
epic O
war O
film O
directed O
by O
Steven B-PERSON
Spielberg I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
Robert B-PERSON
Rodat I-PERSON
Set O
during O
the B-EVENT
Invasion I-EVENT
of I-EVENT
Normandy I-EVENT
in O
World B-EVENT
War I-EVENT
II I-EVENT
the O
film O
is O
known O
for O
its O
graphic O
portrayal O
of O
war O
especially O
its O
depiction O
of O
the O
Omaha B-FAC
Beach I-FAC
assault O
during O
the O
Normandy B-GPE
landings O
The O
film O
follows O
United B-ORG
States I-ORG
Army I-ORG
Rangers O
Captain O
John B-PERSON
H I-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
and O
his O
squad O
as O
they O
search O
for O
a O
paratrooper O
Private O
first O
class O
James B-PERSON
Francis I-PERSON
Ryan I-PERSON
the O
last O
surviving O
brother O
of O
four B-CARDINAL
the O
three B-CARDINAL
other O
brothers O
having O
been O
killed O
in O
action O
The O
film O
was O
a O
co O
production O
between O
DreamWorks B-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
Paramount B-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
Amblin B-ORG
Entertainment I-ORG
and O
Mutual B-ORG
Film I-ORG
Company I-ORG
DreamWorks B-ORG
distributed O
the O
film O
in O
North B-LOC
America I-LOC
while O
Paramount B-ORG
released O
the O
film O
internationally O
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Green I-WORK_OF_ART
Mile I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1999 B-DATE
American B-NORP
magical O
realism O
drama O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Frank B-PERSON
Darabont I-PERSON
and O
based O
on O
Stephen B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
s I-PERSON
1996 B-DATE
novel O
of O
the O
same O
name O
It O
stars O
Tom B-PERSON
Hanks I-PERSON
as O
a O
death O
row O
prison O
guard O
during O
the B-EVENT
Great I-EVENT
Depression I-EVENT
who O
witnesses O
supernatural O
events O
following O
the O
arrival O
of O
an O
enigmatic O
convict O
at O
his O
facility O
David B-PERSON
Morse I-PERSON
Bonnie B-PERSON
Hunt I-PERSON
Doug O
Hutchison O
and O
James B-PERSON
Cromwell I-PERSON
appear O
in O
supporting O
roles O
. O

Life B-WORK_OF_ART
Is I-WORK_OF_ART
Beautiful I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1997 B-DATE
Italian B-NORP
comedy O
drama O
directed O
by O
and O
starring O
Roberto B-PERSON
Benigni I-PERSON
who O
co O
wrote O
the O
film O
with O
Vincenzo B-PERSON
Cerami I-PERSON
Benigni B-PERSON
plays O
Guido B-PERSON
Orefice I-PERSON
a O
Jewish B-NORP
Italian B-NORP
bookshop O
owner O
who O
employs O
his O
fertile O
imagination O
to O
shield O
his O
son O
from O
the O
horrors O
of O
internment O
in O
a O
Nazi B-NORP
concentration O
camp O
The O
film O
was O
partially O
inspired O
by O
the O
book O
In B-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
End I-WORK_OF_ART
I I-WORK_OF_ART
Beat I-WORK_OF_ART
Hitler I-WORK_OF_ART
by O
Rubino B-PERSON
Romeo I-PERSON
Salmonì I-PERSON
and O
by O
Benigni B-PERSON
s O
father O
who O
spent O
two B-DATE
years I-DATE
in O
the O
Bergen B-FAC
Belsen I-FAC
concentration O
camp O
during O
World B-EVENT
War I-EVENT
II I-EVENT
. O

Seven B-CARDINAL
is O
a O
1995 B-DATE
American B-NORP
neo O
noir O
psychological O
crime O
thriller O
film O
directed O
by O
David B-PERSON
Fincher I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
Andrew B-PERSON
Kevin I-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
It O
stars O
Brad B-PERSON
Pitt I-PERSON
Morgan B-PERSON
Freeman I-PERSON
Gwyneth B-PERSON
Paltrow I-PERSON
and O
John B-PERSON
C I-PERSON
McGinley I-PERSON
The O
film O
tells O
the O
story O
of O
David B-PERSON
Mills I-PERSON
Pitt I-PERSON
a O
detective O
who O
partners O
with O
the O
retiring O
William B-PERSON
Somerset I-PERSON
Freeman I-PERSON
to O
track O
down O
a O
serial O
killer O
who O
uses O
the O
seven B-CARDINAL
deadly O
sins O
as O
a O
motif O
in O
his O
murders O
. O

Star B-WORK_OF_ART
Wars I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
an O
American B-NORP
epic O
space O
opera O
multimedia O
franchise O
created O
by O
George B-PERSON
Lucas I-PERSON
which O
began O
with O
the O
eponymous O
1977 B-DATE
film O
and O
quickly O
became O
a O
worldwide O
pop O
culture O
phenomenon O
The O
franchise O
has O
been O
expanded O
into O
various O
films O
and O
other O
media O
including O
television O
series O
video O
games O
novels O
comic O
books O
theme O
park O
attractions O
and O
themed O
areas O
comprising O
an O
all O
encompassing O
fictional O
universe O
In O
2020 B-DATE
its O
total O
value O
was O
estimated O
at O
US B-MONEY
70 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
and O
it O
is O
currently O
the O
fifth B-ORDINAL
highest O
grossing O
media O
franchise O
of O
all O
time O
. O

Seppuku O
sometimes O
referred O
to O
as O
hara O
kiri O
is O
a O
form O
of O
Japanese B-NORP
ritual O
suicide O
by O
disembowelment O
It O
was O
originally O
reserved O
for O
samurai O
in O
their O
code O
of O
honor O
but O
was O
also O
practiced O
by O
other O
Japanese B-NORP
people O
during O
the O
Shōwa O
period O
to O
restore O
honor O
for O
themselves O
or O
for O
their O
families O
As O
a O
samurai O
practice O
seppuku O
was O
used O
voluntarily O
by O
samurai O
to O
die O
with O
honor O
rather O
than O
fall O
into O
the O
hands O
of O
their O
enemies O
as O
a O
form O
of O
capital O
punishment O
for O
samurai O
who O
had O
committed O
serious O
offenses O
or O
performed O
because O
they O
had O
brought O
shame O
to O
themselves O
The O
ceremonial O
disembowelment O
which O
is O
usually O
part O
of O
a O
more O
elaborate O
ritual O
and O
performed O
in O
front O
of O
spectators O
consists O
of O
plunging O
a O
short O
blade O
traditionally O
a O
tantō O
into O
the O
belly O
and O
drawing O
the O
blade O
from O
left O
to O
right O
slicing O
the O
belly O
open O
If O
the O
cut O
is O
deep O
enough O
it O
can O
sever O
the O
abdominal O
aorta O
causing O
a O
rapid O
death O
by O
blood O
loss O
. O

Seven B-WORK_OF_ART
Samurai I-WORK_OF_ART
released O
in O
the B-GPE
United I-GPE
States I-GPE
initially O
as O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Magnificent I-WORK_OF_ART
Seven I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1954 B-DATE
Japanese B-NORP
epic O
samurai O
drama O
film O
co O
written O
edited O
and O
directed O
by O
Akira B-PERSON
Kurosawa I-PERSON
The O
story O
takes O
place O
in O
1586 B-DATE
during O
the O
Sengoku O
period O
of O
Japanese B-NORP
history O
It O
follows O
the O
story O
of O
a O
village O
of O
desperate O
farmers O
who O
hire O
seven B-CARDINAL
rōnin O
to O
combat O
bandits O
who O
will O
return O
after O
the O
harvest O
to O
steal O
their O
crops O
. O

It B-WORK_OF_ART
s I-WORK_OF_ART
a I-WORK_OF_ART
Wonderful I-WORK_OF_ART
Life I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1946 B-DATE
American B-NORP
Christmas B-DATE
fantasy O
drama O
film O
produced O
and O
directed O
by O
Frank B-PERSON
Capra I-PERSON
based O
on O
the O
short O
story O
and O
booklet O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Greatest I-WORK_OF_ART
Gift I-WORK_OF_ART
which O
Philip B-PERSON
Van I-PERSON
Doren I-PERSON
Stern I-PERSON
self O
published O
in O
1943 B-DATE
and O
is O
in O
turn O
loosely O
based O
on O
the O
1843 B-DATE
Charles B-PERSON
Dickens I-PERSON
novella O
A B-WORK_OF_ART
Christmas I-WORK_OF_ART
Carol I-WORK_OF_ART
The O
film O
stars O
James B-PERSON
Stewart I-PERSON
as O
George B-PERSON
Bailey I-PERSON
a O
man O
who O
has O
given O
up O
his O
personal O
dreams O
in O
order O
to O
help O
others O
in O
his O
community O
and O
whose O
thoughts O
of O
suicide O
on O
Christmas B-DATE
Eve I-DATE
brings O
about O
the O
intervention O
of O
his O
guardian O
angel O
Clarence B-PERSON
Odbody I-PERSON
. O

Joker B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2019 B-DATE
American B-NORP
psychological O
thriller O
film O
directed O
and O
produced O
by O
Todd B-PERSON
Phillips I-PERSON
who O
co O
wrote O
the O
screenplay O
with O
Scott B-PERSON
Silver I-PERSON
The O
film O
based O
on O
DC B-ORG
Comics I-ORG
characters O
stars O
Joaquin B-PERSON
Phoenix I-PERSON
as O
the O
Joker B-PERSON
and O
provides O
a O
possible O
origin O
story O
for O
the O
character O
Set O
in O
1981 B-DATE
it O
follows O
Arthur B-PERSON
Fleck I-PERSON
a O
failed O
clown O
and O
aspiring O
stand O
up O
comedian O
whose O
descent O
into O
insanity O
and O
nihilism O
inspires O
a O
violent O
counter O
cultural O
revolution O
against O
the O
wealthy O
in O
a O
decaying O
and O
destroyed O
Gotham B-GPE
City I-GPE
Robert B-PERSON
De I-PERSON
Niro I-PERSON
Zazie B-PERSON
Beetz I-PERSON
Frances B-PERSON
Conroy I-PERSON
Brett B-PERSON
Cullen I-PERSON
Glenn B-PERSON
Fleshler I-PERSON
Bill B-PERSON
Camp I-PERSON
Shea B-PERSON
Whigham I-PERSON
and O
Marc B-PERSON
Maron I-PERSON
appear O
in O
supporting O
roles O
Distributed O
by O
Warner B-ORG
Bros I-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
Joker B-WORK_OF_ART
was O
produced O
by O
Warner B-ORG
Bros I-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
and O
DC B-ORG
Films I-ORG
in O
association O
with O
Village B-ORG
Roadshow I-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
Bron B-ORG
Creative I-ORG
and O
Joint B-ORG
Effort I-ORG
. O

Whiplash B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2014 B-DATE
American B-NORP
psychological O
drama O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Damien B-PERSON
Chazelle I-PERSON
and O
starring O
Miles B-PERSON
Teller I-PERSON
J B-PERSON
K I-PERSON
Simmons I-PERSON
Paul B-PERSON
Reiser I-PERSON
and O
Melissa B-PERSON
Benoist I-PERSON
The O
story O
follows O
ambitious O
jazz O
drummer O
Andrew B-PERSON
Neiman I-PERSON
Teller I-PERSON
who O
is O
pushed O
to O
his O
limit O
by O
his O
abusive O
and O
ruthlessly O
strict O
bandleader O
Simmons B-PERSON
at O
the O
fictional O
Shaffer B-ORG
Conservatory I-ORG
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Intouchables I-WORK_OF_ART
also O
known O
as O
Untouchable B-WORK_OF_ART
in O
the O
UK B-GPE
and O
Ireland B-GPE
is O
a O
French B-NORP
buddy O
comedy O
drama O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Olivier B-PERSON
Nakache I-PERSON
éric I-PERSON
Toledano I-PERSON
It O
stars O
Fran B-PERSON
ois I-PERSON
Cluzet I-PERSON
and O
Omar B-PERSON
Sy I-PERSON
Nine B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
after O
its O
release O
in O
France B-GPE
on O
2 B-DATE
November I-DATE
2011 I-DATE
it O
became O
the O
biggest O
box O
office O
hit O
in O
France B-GPE
just O
passing O
the O
2008 B-DATE
film O
Welcome B-WORK_OF_ART
to I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Sticks I-WORK_OF_ART
The O
film O
was O
voted O
the O
cultural O
event O
of O
2011 B-DATE
in O
France B-GPE
with O
52 B-CARDINAL
of O
votes O
in O
a O
poll O
by O
Fnac B-ORG
Until O
it O
was O
eclipsed O
in O
2014 B-DATE
by O
Lucy B-PERSON
it O
was O
the O
most O
viewed O
French B-NORP
film O
in O
the O
world O
with O
51 B-CARDINAL
5 I-CARDINAL
million I-CARDINAL
tickets O
sold O
The O
film O
received O
several O
award O
nominations O
In O
France B-GPE
the O
film O
won O
the B-WORK_OF_ART
César I-WORK_OF_ART
Award I-WORK_OF_ART
for O
Best O
Actor O
for O
Sy B-PERSON
and O
garnered O
seven B-CARDINAL
further O
nominations O
for O
the B-WORK_OF_ART
César I-WORK_OF_ART
Awards I-WORK_OF_ART
including O
the B-WORK_OF_ART
César I-WORK_OF_ART
Award I-WORK_OF_ART
for O
Best O
Actor O
Five B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
of O
the O
movie O
s O
profit O
were O
given O
to O
Simon B-ORG
de I-ORG
Cyrène I-ORG
an O
association O
that O
helps O
paralyzed O
people O
. O

The O
Prestige O
is O
a O
1995 B-DATE
novel O
by O
British B-NORP
writer O
Christopher B-PERSON
Priest I-PERSON
It O
tells O
the O
story O
of O
a O
prolonged O
feud O
between O
two B-CARDINAL
stage O
magicians O
in O
late B-DATE
1800s I-DATE
England B-GPE
It O
is O
epistolary O
in O
structure O
that O
is O
it O
purports O
to O
be O
a O
collection O
of O
real O
diaries O
that O
were O
kept O
by O
the O
protagonists O
and O
later O
collated O
The O
title O
derives O
from O
the O
novel O
s O
fictional O
practice O
of O
stage O
illusions O
having O
three B-CARDINAL
parts O
the O
setup O
the O
performance O
and O
the O
prestige O
effect O
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Departed I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2006 B-DATE
American B-NORP
epic O
crime O
thriller O
film O
directed O
by O
Martin B-PERSON
Scorsese I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
William B-PERSON
Monahan I-PERSON
It O
is O
simultaneously O
a O
remake O
of O
the O
2002 B-DATE
Hong B-GPE
Kong I-GPE
film O
Infernal B-WORK_OF_ART
Affairs I-WORK_OF_ART
and O
is O
also O
loosely O
based O
on O
the O
real O
life O
Boston B-ORG
Winter I-ORG
Hill I-ORG
Gang I-ORG
the O
character O
Colin B-PERSON
Sullivan I-PERSON
is O
based O
on O
the O
corrupt O
FBI B-ORG
agent O
John B-PERSON
Connolly I-PERSON
while O
the O
character O
Frank B-PERSON
Costello I-PERSON
is O
based O
on O
Irish B-NORP
American B-NORP
gangster O
Whitey B-PERSON
Bulger I-PERSON
The O
film O
stars O
Leonardo B-PERSON
DiCaprio I-PERSON
Matt B-PERSON
Damon I-PERSON
Jack B-PERSON
Nicholson I-PERSON
and O
Mark B-PERSON
Wahlberg I-PERSON
with O
Martin B-PERSON
Sheen I-PERSON
Ray B-PERSON
Winstone I-PERSON
Vera B-PERSON
Farmiga I-PERSON
and O
Alec B-PERSON
Baldwin I-PERSON
in O
supporting O
roles O
. O

A O
pianist O
is O
someone O
who O
plays O
the O
piano O
. O

American B-WORK_OF_ART
History I-WORK_OF_ART
X I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1998 B-DATE
American B-NORP
crime O
drama O
film O
directed O
by O
Tony B-PERSON
Kaye I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
David B-PERSON
McKenna I-PERSON
The O
film O
stars O
Edward B-PERSON
Norton I-PERSON
and O
Edward B-PERSON
Furlong I-PERSON
as O
two B-CARDINAL
brothers O
from O
Los B-GPE
Angeles I-GPE
who O
are O
involved O
in O
the O
white O
power O
skinhead O
and O
neo B-NORP
Nazi I-NORP
movements O
The O
older O
brother O
Norton B-PERSON
serves O
three B-DATE
years I-DATE
in O
prison O
for O
voluntary O
manslaughter O
and O
is O
rehabilitated O
during O
this O
time O
and O
then O
tries O
to O
prevent O
his O
brother O
Furlong B-PERSON
from O
being O
indoctrinated O
further O
The O
supporting O
cast O
includes O
Fairuza B-PERSON
Balk I-PERSON
Stacy B-PERSON
Keach I-PERSON
Elliott B-PERSON
Gould I-PERSON
Avery B-PERSON
Brooks I-PERSON
Ethan B-PERSON
Suplee I-PERSON
and O
Beverly B-PERSON
D I-PERSON
Angelo I-PERSON
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Usual I-WORK_OF_ART
Suspects I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1995 B-DATE
neo O
noir O
mystery O
thriller O
film O
directed O
by O
Bryan B-PERSON
Singer I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
Christopher B-PERSON
McQuarrie I-PERSON
It O
stars O
Stephen B-PERSON
Baldwin I-PERSON
Gabriel B-PERSON
Byrne I-PERSON
Benicio B-PERSON
del I-PERSON
Toro I-PERSON
Kevin B-PERSON
Pollak I-PERSON
Chazz B-PERSON
Palminteri I-PERSON
Pete B-PERSON
Postlethwaite I-PERSON
and O
Kevin B-PERSON
Spacey I-PERSON
. O

Léon B-WORK_OF_ART
The I-WORK_OF_ART
Professional I-WORK_OF_ART
titled O
Leon B-WORK_OF_ART
in O
the O
UK B-GPE
and O
Australia B-GPE
is O
a O
1994 B-DATE
English B-LANGUAGE
language O
French B-NORP
action O
thriller O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Luc B-PERSON
Besson I-PERSON
It O
stars O
Jean B-PERSON
Reno I-PERSON
and O
Gary B-PERSON
Oldman I-PERSON
and O
features O
the O
film O
debut O
of O
Natalie B-PERSON
Portman I-PERSON
The O
plot O
follows O
Léon B-PERSON
Reno I-PERSON
a O
professional O
hitman O
who O
reluctantly O
takes O
in O
twelve B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
Mathilda B-PERSON
Portman I-PERSON
after O
her O
family O
is O
murdered O
by O
corrupt O
Drug B-ORG
Enforcement I-ORG
Administration I-ORG
agent O
Norman B-PERSON
Stansfield I-PERSON
Oldman I-PERSON
Léon B-PERSON
and O
Mathilda B-PERSON
form O
an O
unusual O
relationship O
as O
she O
becomes O
his O
protégée O
and O
learns O
the O
hitman O
s O
trade O
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Lion I-WORK_OF_ART
King I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1994 B-DATE
American B-NORP
animated O
musical O
drama O
film O
produced O
by O
Walt B-ORG
Disney I-ORG
Feature I-ORG
Animation I-ORG
and O
released O
by O
Walt B-ORG
Disney I-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
It O
is O
the O
32nd B-ORDINAL
Disney B-ORG
animated O
feature O
film O
and O
the O
fifth B-ORDINAL
animated O
film O
produced O
during O
a O
period O
known O
as O
the B-EVENT
Disney I-EVENT
Renaissance I-EVENT
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Lion I-WORK_OF_ART
King I-WORK_OF_ART
was O
directed O
by O
Roger B-PERSON
Allers I-PERSON
and O
Rob B-PERSON
Minkoff I-PERSON
and O
produced O
by O
Don B-PERSON
Hahn I-PERSON
from O
a O
screenplay O
by O
Irene B-PERSON
Mecchi I-PERSON
Jonathan B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
and O
Linda B-PERSON
Woolverton I-PERSON
Its O
original O
songs O
were O
written O
by O
composer O
Elton B-PERSON
John I-PERSON
and O
lyricist O
Tim B-PERSON
Rice I-PERSON
with O
a O
score O
by O
Hans B-PERSON
Zimmer I-PERSON
The O
film O
features O
an O
ensemble O
voice O
cast O
that O
includes O
Matthew B-PERSON
Broderick I-PERSON
James B-PERSON
Earl I-PERSON
Jones I-PERSON
Jeremy B-PERSON
Irons I-PERSON
Jonathan B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
Thomas B-PERSON
Moira I-PERSON
Kelly B-PERSON
Nathan B-PERSON
Lane I-PERSON
Ernie B-PERSON
Sabella I-PERSON
Rowan B-PERSON
Atkinson I-PERSON
Robert B-PERSON
Guillaume I-PERSON
Madge B-PERSON
Sinclair I-PERSON
Whoopi B-PERSON
Goldberg I-PERSON
Cheech B-PERSON
Marin I-PERSON
and O
Jim B-PERSON
Cummings I-PERSON
The O
story O
takes O
place O
in O
a O
kingdom O
of O
lions O
in O
Africa B-LOC
and O
was O
influenced O
by O
the O
Biblical B-NORP
stories O
of O
Joseph B-PERSON
and O
Moses B-PERSON
and O
William B-PERSON
Shakespeare I-PERSON
s I-PERSON
Hamlet B-WORK_OF_ART
. O

Terminator B-WORK_OF_ART
2 I-WORK_OF_ART
Judgment B-WORK_OF_ART
Day I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1991 B-DATE
American B-NORP
science O
fiction O
action O
film O
produced O
and O
directed O
by O
James B-PERSON
Cameron I-PERSON
who O
co O
wrote O
the O
script O
with O
William B-PERSON
Wisher I-PERSON
Starring O
Arnold B-PERSON
Schwarzenegger I-PERSON
Linda B-PERSON
Hamilton I-PERSON
Robert B-PERSON
Patrick I-PERSON
and O
Edward B-PERSON
Furlong I-PERSON
Terminator B-WORK_OF_ART
2 I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
the O
sequel O
to O
the O
1984 B-DATE
film O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Terminator I-WORK_OF_ART
and O
the O
second B-ORDINAL
installment O
in O
the O
Terminator B-WORK_OF_ART
franchise O
In O
its O
plot O
the O
malevolent O
artificial O
intelligence O
Skynet B-PRODUCT
sends O
a O
Terminator B-PRODUCT
a O
highly O
advanced O
killing O
machine O
back O
in O
time O
to O
1995 B-DATE
to O
kill O
the O
future O
leader O
of O
the O
human O
resistance O
John B-PERSON
Connor I-PERSON
when O
he O
is O
a O
child O
The O
resistance O
sends O
back O
a O
less O
advanced O
reprogrammed O
Terminator B-PRODUCT
to O
protect O
Connor B-PERSON
and O
ensure O
the O
future O
of O
humanity O
. O

Cinema B-WORK_OF_ART
Paradiso I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1988 B-DATE
coming O
of O
age O
drama O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Giuseppe B-PERSON
Tornatore I-PERSON
Set O
in O
a O
small O
Sicilian B-NORP
town O
the O
film O
centers O
on O
the O
friendship O
between O
a O
young O
boy O
and O
an O
aging O
projectionist O
who O
works O
at O
the O
titular O
movie O
theatre O
This O
Italian B-NORP
French B-NORP
co O
production O
stars O
Philippe B-PERSON
Noiret I-PERSON
Jacques I-PERSON
Perrin I-PERSON
Leopoldo I-PERSON
Trieste I-PERSON
Marco B-PERSON
Leonardi I-PERSON
Agnese I-PERSON
Nano I-PERSON
and O
Salvatore B-PERSON
Cascio I-PERSON
with O
a O
musical O
score O
was O
composed O
by O
Ennio B-PERSON
Morricone I-PERSON
along O
with O
his O
son O
Andrea B-PERSON
. O

Grave B-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Fireflies I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1988 B-DATE
Japanese B-NORP
animated O
war O
tragedy O
film O
based O
on O
the O
1967 B-DATE
semi O
autobiographical O
short O
story O
of O
the O
same O
name O
by O
Akiyuki B-PERSON
Nosaka I-PERSON
It O
was O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Isao B-PERSON
Takahata I-PERSON
and O
animated O
by O
Studio B-ORG
Ghibli I-ORG
for O
the O
story O
s O
publisher O
Shinchosha B-ORG
Publishing O
The O
film O
stars O
Tsutomu B-PERSON
Tatsumi I-PERSON
Ayano I-PERSON
Shiraishi I-PERSON
Yoshiko B-PERSON
Shinohara I-PERSON
and O
Akemi B-PERSON
Yamaguchi I-PERSON
Set O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kobe B-GPE
Japan B-GPE
the O
film O
tells O
the O
story O
of O
two B-CARDINAL
siblings O
Seita B-PERSON
and O
Setsuko B-PERSON
and O
their O
desperate O
struggle O
to O
survive O
during O
the B-DATE
final I-DATE
months I-DATE
of O
the B-EVENT
Second I-EVENT
World I-EVENT
War I-EVENT
Grave B-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Fireflies I-WORK_OF_ART
received O
critical O
acclaim O
and O
has O
been O
ranked O
as O
one B-CARDINAL
of O
the O
greatest O
war O
films O
of O
all O
time O
and O
has O
been O
recognized O
as O
a O
major O
work O
of O
Japanese B-NORP
animation O
. O

Back B-WORK_OF_ART
to I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Future I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1985 B-DATE
American B-NORP
science O
fiction O
film O
directed O
by O
Robert B-PERSON
Zemeckis I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
Zemeckis B-PERSON
and O
Bob B-PERSON
Gale I-PERSON
It O
stars O
Michael B-PERSON
J I-PERSON
Fox I-PERSON
Christopher B-PERSON
Lloyd I-PERSON
Lea B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
Crispin B-PERSON
Glover I-PERSON
and O
Thomas B-PERSON
F I-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
Set O
in O
1985 B-DATE
the O
story O
follows O
Marty B-PERSON
McFly I-PERSON
Fox I-PERSON
a O
teenager O
accidentally O
sent O
back O
to O
1955 B-DATE
in O
a O
time O
traveling O
DeLorean B-PRODUCT
automobile O
built O
by O
his O
eccentric O
scientist O
friend O
Doctor O
Emmett B-PERSON
Doc I-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
Lloyd I-PERSON
Trapped O
in O
the O
past O
Marty B-PERSON
inadvertently O
prevents O
his O
future O
parents O
meeting O
threatening O
his O
existence O
and O
is O
forced O
to O
reconcile O
the O
pair O
and O
somehow O
get O
back O
to O
the O
future O
. O

Once B-WORK_OF_ART
Upon I-WORK_OF_ART
a I-WORK_OF_ART
Time I-WORK_OF_ART
in I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
West I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1968 B-DATE
epic O
Spaghetti O
Western O
film O
directed O
by O
Sergio B-PERSON
Leone I-PERSON
who O
co O
wrote O
it O
with O
Sergio B-PERSON
Donati I-PERSON
based O
on O
a O
story O
by O
Dario B-PERSON
Argento I-PERSON
Bernardo B-PERSON
Bertolucci I-PERSON
and O
Leone B-PERSON
It O
stars O
Henry B-PERSON
Fonda I-PERSON
cast O
against O
type O
as O
the O
villain O
Charles B-PERSON
Bronson I-PERSON
as O
his O
nemesis O
Jason B-PERSON
Robards I-PERSON
as O
a O
bandit O
and O
Claudia B-PERSON
Cardinale I-PERSON
as O
a O
newly O
widowed O
homesteader O
The O
widescreen O
cinematography O
was O
by O
Tonino B-PERSON
Delli I-PERSON
Colli I-PERSON
and O
the O
acclaimed O
film O
score O
was O
by O
Ennio B-PERSON
Morricone I-PERSON
. O

Psycho B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1960 B-DATE
American B-NORP
psychological O
horror O
thriller O
film O
produced O
and O
directed O
by O
Alfred B-PERSON
Hitchcock I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
Joseph B-PERSON
Stefano I-PERSON
It O
is O
a O
film O
adaptation O
of O
the O
1959 B-DATE
novel O
of O
the O
same O
name O
by O
Robert B-PERSON
Bloch I-PERSON
The O
film O
stars O
Anthony B-PERSON
Perkins I-PERSON
Janet B-PERSON
Leigh I-PERSON
Vera B-PERSON
Miles I-PERSON
John B-PERSON
Gavin I-PERSON
and O
Martin B-PERSON
Balsam I-PERSON
The O
plot O
centers O
on O
an O
encounter O
between O
on O
the O
run O
embezzler O
Marion B-PERSON
Crane I-PERSON
Leigh I-PERSON
and O
shy O
motel O
proprietor O
Norman B-PERSON
Bates I-PERSON
Perkins I-PERSON
and O
its O
aftermath O
in O
which O
a O
private O
investigator O
Balsam B-PERSON
Marion I-PERSON
s O
lover O
Sam B-PERSON
Loomis I-PERSON
Gavin I-PERSON
and O
her O
sister O
Lila B-PERSON
Miles I-PERSON
investigate O
the O
cause O
of O
her O
disappearance O
. O

Casablanca B-GPE
also O
known O
in O
Arabic B-LANGUAGE
as O
Dar B-GPE
al I-GPE
Bayda I-GPE
is O
the O
largest O
city O
of O
Morocco B-GPE
Located O
on O
the B-LOC
Atlantic I-LOC
coast I-LOC
of O
the B-LOC
Chaouia I-LOC
plain I-LOC
in O
the O
central O
western O
part O
of O
Morocco B-GPE
Casablanca B-GPE
is O
considered O
a O
Global O
Financial O
Centre O
ranking O
53rd B-ORDINAL
globally O
in O
the O
Global O
Financial O
Centres O
Index O
for O
the B-DATE
year I-DATE
2021 I-DATE
outperforming O
many O
cities O
such O
as O
Mumbai B-GPE
New B-GPE
Delhi I-GPE
Berlin B-GPE
Istanbul B-GPE
Mexico B-GPE
City I-GPE
Glasgow B-GPE
Jakarta B-GPE
Rio B-GPE
de I-GPE
Janeiro I-GPE
S O
o O
Paulo O
Riyadh B-GPE
Doha B-GPE
Kuwait B-GPE
City I-GPE
Cape B-GPE
Town I-GPE
and O
Johannesburg B-GPE
Casablanca B-GPE
is O
ranked O
among O
the O
Emerging O
International O
contenders O
and O
it O
is O
considered O
the O
largest O
financial O
center O
in O
Africa B-LOC
it O
is O
the O
largest O
city O
in O
the B-LOC
Maghreb I-LOC
region I-LOC
With O
a O
total O
population O
of O
3 B-CARDINAL
359 I-CARDINAL
818 I-CARDINAL
people O
according O
to O
the O
2014 B-DATE
General B-EVENT
Population I-EVENT
and I-EVENT
Housing I-EVENT
Census I-EVENT
and O
4 B-CARDINAL
270 I-CARDINAL
750 I-CARDINAL
people O
in O
its O
total O
population O
making O
it O
the O
most O
populous O
city O
in O
the O
Kingdom B-GPE
and O
the O
eighth B-ORDINAL
largest O
in O
the O
Arab B-NORP
world O
Casablanca B-GPE
is O
Morocco B-GPE
s O
chief O
port O
and O
the O
largest O
financial O
centers O
in O
Africa B-LOC
According O
to O
the O
2019 B-DATE
population O
estimate O
the O
city O
has O
a O
population O
of O
about B-CARDINAL
3 I-CARDINAL
71 I-CARDINAL
million I-CARDINAL
in O
the O
urban O
area O
and O
over B-CARDINAL
4 I-CARDINAL
27 I-CARDINAL
million I-CARDINAL
in O
the O
Greater O
Casablanca B-GPE
Casablanca B-GPE
is O
considered O
the O
economic O
and O
business O
center O
of O
Morocco B-GPE
although O
the O
national O
political O
capital O
is O
Rabat B-GPE
. O

Modern B-WORK_OF_ART
Times I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1936 B-DATE
American B-NORP
silent O
comedy O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Charlie B-PERSON
Chaplin I-PERSON
in O
which O
his O
iconic O
Little O
Tramp B-PERSON
character O
struggles O
to O
survive O
in O
the O
modern O
industrialized O
world O
The O
film O
is O
a O
commentary O
on O
the O
desperate O
employment O
and O
financial O
conditions O
many O
people O
faced O
during O
the O
Great B-EVENT
Depression I-EVENT
conditions O
created O
in O
Chaplin B-PERSON
s O
view O
by O
the O
efficiencies O
of O
modern O
industrialization O
The O
movie O
stars O
Chaplin B-PERSON
Paulette B-PERSON
Goddard I-PERSON
Henry B-PERSON
Bergman I-PERSON
Tiny B-PERSON
Sandford I-PERSON
and O
Chester B-PERSON
Conklin I-PERSON
It O
is O
notable O
for O
being O
the O
last O
time O
that O
Chaplin B-PERSON
portrayed O
the O
Tramp B-PERSON
character O
and O
for O
being O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
time O
Chaplin B-PERSON
s O
voice O
is O
heard O
on O
film O
. O

City B-WORK_OF_ART
Lights I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1931 B-DATE
American B-NORP
silent O
romantic O
comedy O
film O
written O
produced O
directed O
by O
and O
starring O
Charlie B-PERSON
Chaplin I-PERSON
The O
story O
follows O
the O
misadventures O
of O
Chaplin B-PERSON
s O
Tramp B-PERSON
as O
he O
falls O
in O
love O
with O
a O
blind O
girl O
and O
develops O
a O
turbulent O
friendship O
with O
an O
alcoholic O
millionaire O
. O

Capernaum B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2018 B-DATE
Lebanese B-NORP
drama O
film O
directed O
by O
Nadine B-PERSON
Labaki I-PERSON
and O
produced O
by O
Khaled B-PERSON
Mouzanar I-PERSON
The O
screenplay O
was O
written O
by O
Labaki B-PERSON
Jihad I-PERSON
Hojaily I-PERSON
and O
Michelle B-PERSON
Keserwany I-PERSON
from O
a O
story O
by O
Labaki B-PERSON
Hojaily I-PERSON
Keserwany I-PERSON
Georges I-PERSON
Khabbaz I-PERSON
and O
Khaled B-PERSON
Mouzanar I-PERSON
The O
film O
stars O
Syrian B-NORP
refugee O
child O
actor O
Zain B-PERSON
Al I-PERSON
Rafeea I-PERSON
as O
Zain B-PERSON
El I-PERSON
Hajj I-PERSON
a O
12 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
living O
in O
the O
slums O
of O
Beirut B-GPE
Capernaum B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
told O
in O
flashback O
format O
focusing O
on O
Zain B-PERSON
s O
life O
including O
his O
encounter O
with O
an O
Ethiopian B-NORP
immigrant O
Rahil B-PERSON
and O
her O
infant O
son O
Yonas B-PERSON
and O
leading O
up O
to O
his O
attempt O
to O
sue O
his O
parents O
for O
child O
neglect O
. O

Vikram B-WORK_OF_ART
Vedha I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2017 B-DATE
Indian B-NORP
Tamil B-LANGUAGE
language O
neo O
noir O
action O
thriller O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Pushkar B-PERSON
Gayathri I-PERSON
and O
produced O
by O
S B-PERSON
Sashikanth I-PERSON
under O
his O
banner O
YNOT B-ORG
Studios I-ORG
The O
film O
stars O
Madhavan B-PERSON
Vijay I-PERSON
Sethupathi I-PERSON
Shraddha B-PERSON
Srinath I-PERSON
Kathir I-PERSON
and O
Varalaxmi B-PERSON
Sarathkumar I-PERSON
while O
Prem B-PERSON
Achyuth I-PERSON
Kumar I-PERSON
Hareesh I-PERSON
Peradi I-PERSON
and O
Vivek B-PERSON
Prasanna I-PERSON
play O
supporting O
roles O
Inspired O
by O
the O
Indian B-NORP
folktale O
Baital B-WORK_OF_ART
Pachisi I-WORK_OF_ART
the O
film O
tells O
the O
story O
of O
Vikram B-PERSON
Madhavan I-PERSON
a O
police O
inspector O
who O
sets O
out O
to O
track O
down O
and O
kill O
Vedha B-PERSON
Sethupathi I-PERSON
a O
gangster O
After O
Vedha B-PERSON
voluntarily O
surrenders O
himself O
he O
tells O
Vikram B-PERSON
three B-CARDINAL
stories O
which O
change O
his O
perceptions O
of O
good O
and O
evil O
. O

Your B-WORK_OF_ART
Name I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2016 B-DATE
Japanese B-NORP
animated O
romantic O
fantasy O
film O
produced O
by O
CoMix B-ORG
Wave I-ORG
Films I-ORG
and O
released O
by O
Toho B-ORG
It O
depicts O
a O
high O
school O
boy O
in O
Tokyo B-GPE
and O
a O
high O
school O
girl O
in O
the O
Japanese B-NORP
countryside O
who O
suddenly O
and O
inexplicably O
begin O
to O
swap O
bodies O
. O

Dangal B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2016 B-DATE
Indian B-NORP
Hindi B-LANGUAGE
language O
biographical O
sports O
drama O
film O
directed O
by O
Nitesh B-PERSON
Tiwari I-PERSON
and O
produced O
by O
Aamir B-PERSON
Khan I-PERSON
and O
Kiran B-PERSON
Rao I-PERSON
under O
Aamir B-ORG
Khan I-ORG
Productions I-ORG
with O
Siddharth B-PERSON
Roy I-PERSON
Kapur I-PERSON
under O
The B-ORG
Walt I-ORG
Disney I-ORG
Company I-ORG
India I-ORG
The O
film O
stars O
Khan B-PERSON
as O
Mahavir B-PERSON
Singh I-PERSON
Phogat I-PERSON
a O
pehlwani O
amateur O
wrestler O
who O
trains O
his O
daughters O
Geeta B-PERSON
Phogat I-PERSON
and O
Babita B-PERSON
Kumari I-PERSON
to O
become O
India B-GPE
s O
first B-ORDINAL
world O
class O
female O
wrestlers O
Fatima B-PERSON
Sana I-PERSON
Shaikh I-PERSON
and O
Sanya B-PERSON
Malhotra I-PERSON
portray O
the O
adult O
versions O
of O
the O
two B-CARDINAL
Phogat B-PERSON
sisters O
Zaira B-PERSON
Wasim I-PERSON
and O
Suhani B-PERSON
Bhatnagar I-PERSON
their O
younger O
versions O
Sakshi B-PERSON
Tanwar I-PERSON
their O
mother O
and O
Aparshakti B-PERSON
Khurana I-PERSON
their O
cousin O
all O
of O
them O
except O
Tanwar B-PERSON
in O
their O
film O
debuts O
. O

Spider B-WORK_OF_ART
Man I-WORK_OF_ART
Into I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Spider I-WORK_OF_ART
Verse I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2018 B-DATE
American B-NORP
computer O
animated O
superhero O
film O
featuring O
the O
Marvel B-ORG
Comics I-ORG
character O
Miles B-PERSON
Morales I-PERSON
Spider O
Man O
produced O
by O
Columbia B-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
and O
Sony B-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
Animation I-ORG
in O
association O
with O
Marvel B-ORG
Entertainment I-ORG
Distributed O
by O
Sony B-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
Releasing I-ORG
it O
is O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
animated O
film O
in O
the O
Spider B-PERSON
Man I-PERSON
franchise O
Directed O
by O
Bob B-PERSON
Persichetti I-PERSON
Peter I-PERSON
Ramsey I-PERSON
and O
Rodney B-PERSON
Rothman I-PERSON
from O
a O
screenplay O
by O
Phil B-PERSON
Lord I-PERSON
and O
Rothman B-PERSON
it O
stars O
Shameik B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
as O
Morales B-PERSON
alongside O
the O
voices O
of O
Jake B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
Hailee B-PERSON
Steinfeld I-PERSON
Mahershala B-PERSON
Ali I-PERSON
Brian B-PERSON
Tyree I-PERSON
Henry B-PERSON
Lily B-PERSON
Tomlin I-PERSON
Luna B-PERSON
Lauren B-PERSON
Vélez I-PERSON
John B-PERSON
Mulaney I-PERSON
Kimiko B-PERSON
Glenn B-PERSON
Nicolas B-PERSON
Cage I-PERSON
and O
Liev B-PERSON
Schreiber I-PERSON
The O
film O
s O
story O
follows O
Miles B-PERSON
Morales I-PERSON
as O
he O
becomes O
the O
new O
Spider O
Man O
and O
joins O
other O
Spider O
People O
from O
various O
parallel O
universes O
to O
save O
his O
universe O
from O
Kingpin B-PERSON
. O

Avengers B-WORK_OF_ART
Endgame I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2019 B-DATE
American B-NORP
superhero O
film O
based O
on O
the O
Marvel B-ORG
Comics I-ORG
superhero O
team O
the O
Avengers B-ORG
Produced O
by O
Marvel B-ORG
Studios I-ORG
and O
distributed O
by O
Walt B-ORG
Disney I-ORG
Studios I-ORG
Motion I-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
it O
is O
the O
direct O
sequel O
to O
Avengers B-WORK_OF_ART
Infinity I-WORK_OF_ART
War I-WORK_OF_ART
2018 I-WORK_OF_ART
and O
the O
22nd B-ORDINAL
film O
in O
the O
Marvel O
Cinematic O
Universe O
MCU O
Directed O
by O
Anthony B-PERSON
and O
Joe B-PERSON
Russo I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
Christopher B-PERSON
Markus I-PERSON
and O
Stephen B-PERSON
McFeely I-PERSON
the O
film O
features O
an O
ensemble O
cast O
including O
Robert B-PERSON
Downey I-PERSON
Jr I-PERSON
Chris B-PERSON
Evans I-PERSON
Mark B-PERSON
Ruffalo I-PERSON
Chris B-PERSON
Hemsworth I-PERSON
Scarlett B-PERSON
Johansson I-PERSON
Jeremy B-PERSON
Renner I-PERSON
Don B-PERSON
Cheadle I-PERSON
Paul B-PERSON
Rudd I-PERSON
Brie B-PERSON
Larson I-PERSON
Karen B-PERSON
Gillan I-PERSON
Danai B-PERSON
Gurira I-PERSON
Benedict B-PERSON
Wong I-PERSON
Jon B-PERSON
Favreau I-PERSON
Bradley B-PERSON
Cooper I-PERSON
Gwyneth B-PERSON
Paltrow I-PERSON
and O
Josh B-PERSON
Brolin I-PERSON
In O
the O
film O
the O
surviving O
members O
of O
the O
Avengers B-ORG
and O
their O
allies O
attempt O
to O
reverse O
the O
destruction O
caused O
by O
Thanos B-PERSON
in O
Infinity B-EVENT
War I-EVENT
. O

Coco O
commonly O
refers O
to O
Coco O
folklore O
a O
mythical O
bogeyman O
in O
many O
Hispano B-NORP
and O
Lusophone B-NORP
nations O
. O

Django B-WORK_OF_ART
Unchained I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2012 B-DATE
American B-NORP
revisionist O
Western O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Quentin B-PERSON
Tarantino I-PERSON
starring O
Jamie B-PERSON
Foxx I-PERSON
Christoph B-PERSON
Waltz I-PERSON
Leonardo B-PERSON
DiCaprio I-PERSON
Kerry B-PERSON
Washington I-PERSON
and O
Samuel B-PERSON
L I-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
with O
Walton B-PERSON
Goggins I-PERSON
Dennis B-PERSON
Christopher I-PERSON
James I-PERSON
Remar I-PERSON
Michael B-PERSON
Parks I-PERSON
and O
Don B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
in O
supporting O
roles O
Set O
in O
the B-LOC
Old I-LOC
West I-LOC
and O
Antebellum B-LOC
South I-LOC
it O
is O
a O
highly O
stylized O
heavily O
revisionist O
tribute O
to O
Spaghetti O
Westerns O
in O
particular O
the O
1966 B-DATE
Italian B-NORP
film O
Django B-WORK_OF_ART
by O
Sergio B-PERSON
Corbucci I-PERSON
whose O
star O
Franco B-PERSON
Nero I-PERSON
has O
a O
cameo O
appearance O
The O
story O
follows O
a O
black O
slave O
who O
trains O
under O
a O
German B-NORP
bounty O
hunter O
with O
the O
ultimate O
goal O
of O
reuniting O
with O
his O
long O
lost O
wife O
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Dark I-WORK_OF_ART
Knight I-WORK_OF_ART
Rises I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2012 B-DATE
superhero O
film O
directed O
by O
Christopher B-PERSON
Nolan I-PERSON
who O
co O
wrote O
the O
screenplay O
with O
his O
brother O
Jonathan B-PERSON
Nolan I-PERSON
and O
the O
story O
with O
David B-PERSON
S I-PERSON
Goyer I-PERSON
Based O
on O
the O
DC B-ORG
Comics I-ORG
character O
Batman B-PERSON
it O
is O
the O
final O
installment O
in O
Nolan B-PERSON
s O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Dark I-WORK_OF_ART
Knight I-WORK_OF_ART
trilogy O
and O
the O
sequel O
to O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Dark I-WORK_OF_ART
Knight I-WORK_OF_ART
2008 B-DATE
The O
film O
stars O
Christian B-PERSON
Bale I-PERSON
as O
Bruce B-PERSON
Wayne I-PERSON
Batman O
alongside O
Tom B-PERSON
Hardy I-PERSON
Gary B-PERSON
Oldman I-PERSON
Marion B-PERSON
Cotillard I-PERSON
Morgan B-PERSON
Freeman I-PERSON
Joseph B-PERSON
Gordon I-PERSON
Levitt I-PERSON
Michael B-PERSON
Caine I-PERSON
and O
Anne B-PERSON
Hathaway I-PERSON
Eight B-DATE
years I-DATE
after O
the O
events O
of O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Dark I-WORK_OF_ART
Knight I-WORK_OF_ART
the O
revolutionary O
Bane B-PERSON
forces O
Bruce B-PERSON
Wayne I-PERSON
to O
resume O
his O
role O
as O
Batman B-PERSON
and O
save O
Gotham B-GPE
City I-GPE
from O
nuclear O
destruction O
. O

3 B-WORK_OF_ART
Idiots I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2009 B-DATE
Indian B-NORP
Hindi B-LANGUAGE
language O
coming O
of O
age O
comedy O
drama O
film O
written O
edited O
and O
directed O
by O
Rajkumar B-PERSON
Hirani I-PERSON
and O
co O
written O
by O
Abhijat B-PERSON
Joshi I-PERSON
with O
producer O
Vidhu B-PERSON
Vinod I-PERSON
Chopra I-PERSON
acting O
as O
a O
screenplay O
associate O
Adapted O
loosely O
from O
Chetan B-PERSON
Bhagat I-PERSON
s I-PERSON
novel O
Five B-WORK_OF_ART
Point I-WORK_OF_ART
Someone I-WORK_OF_ART
the O
film O
stars O
Aamir B-PERSON
Khan I-PERSON
R I-PERSON
Madhavan I-PERSON
and O
Sharman B-PERSON
Joshi I-PERSON
in O
the O
titular O
roles O
marking O
their O
reunion O
three B-DATE
years I-DATE
after O
the O
2006 B-DATE
film O
Rang B-WORK_OF_ART
De I-WORK_OF_ART
Basanti I-WORK_OF_ART
while O
Omi B-PERSON
Vaidya I-PERSON
Kareena I-PERSON
Kapoor I-PERSON
and O
Boman B-PERSON
Irani I-PERSON
star O
in O
pivotal O
roles O
Narrated O
through O
parallel O
dramas O
one B-CARDINAL
in O
the O
present O
and O
the O
other O
ten B-DATE
years I-DATE
in O
the O
past O
the O
story O
follows O
the O
friendship O
of O
three B-CARDINAL
students O
at O
an O
Indian B-NORP
engineering O
college O
and O
is O
a O
satire O
about O
the O
social O
pressures O
under O
an O
Indian B-NORP
education O
system O
. O

Taare B-WORK_OF_ART
Zameen I-WORK_OF_ART
Par I-WORK_OF_ART
also O
known O
as O
Like B-WORK_OF_ART
Stars I-WORK_OF_ART
on I-WORK_OF_ART
Earth I-WORK_OF_ART
in O
English B-LANGUAGE
is O
a O
2007 B-DATE
Indian B-NORP
Hindi B-LANGUAGE
language O
drama O
film O
produced O
and O
directed O
by O
Aamir B-PERSON
Khan I-PERSON
The O
film O
stars O
Khan B-PERSON
himself O
along O
with O
Darsheel B-PERSON
Safary I-PERSON
Tanay I-PERSON
Chheda I-PERSON
Sachet I-PERSON
Engineer O
Vipin B-PERSON
Sharma I-PERSON
and O
Tisca B-PERSON
Chopra I-PERSON
The O
film O
explores O
the O
life O
and O
imagination O
of O
Ishaan B-PERSON
Safary I-PERSON
an O
8 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
dyslexic O
child O
Although O
he O
excels O
in O
art O
his O
poor O
academic O
performance O
leads O
his O
parents O
to O
send O
him O
to O
a O
boarding O
school O
Ishaan B-PERSON
s O
new O
art O
teacher O
Nikumbh B-PERSON
suspects O
that O
he O
is O
dyslexic O
and O
helps O
him O
to O
overcome O
his O
reading O
disorder O
. O

WALL B-WORK_OF_ART
E I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2008 B-DATE
American B-NORP
computer O
animated O
science O
fiction O
film O
produced O
by O
Pixar B-ORG
Animation I-ORG
Studios I-ORG
and O
released O
by O
Walt B-ORG
Disney I-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
It O
was O
directed O
and O
co O
written O
by O
Andrew B-PERSON
Stanton I-PERSON
produced O
by O
Jim B-PERSON
Morris I-PERSON
and O
co O
written O
by O
Jim B-PERSON
Reardon I-PERSON
It O
stars O
the O
voices O
of O
Ben B-PERSON
Burtt I-PERSON
Elissa B-PERSON
Knight I-PERSON
Jeff B-PERSON
Garlin I-PERSON
John B-PERSON
Ratzenberger I-PERSON
Kathy B-PERSON
Najimy I-PERSON
and O
Sigourney B-PERSON
Weaver I-PERSON
with O
Fred B-PERSON
Willard I-PERSON
in O
the O
film O
s O
only O
prominent O
live O
action O
role O
The O
overall O
ninth B-ORDINAL
feature O
film O
produced O
by O
the O
studio O
WALL B-ORG
E I-ORG
follows O
a O
solitary O
robot O
on O
a O
future O
uninhabitable O
deserted O
Earth B-LOC
in O
2805 B-DATE
left O
to O
clean O
up O
garbage O
However O
he O
is O
visited O
by O
a O
probe O
sent O
by O
the O
starship O
Axiom B-PRODUCT
a O
robot O
called O
EVE B-PRODUCT
with O
whom O
he O
falls O
in O
love O
and O
pursues O
across O
the O
galaxy O
. O

Oldboy B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2003 B-DATE
South B-NORP
Korean I-NORP
neo O
noir O
action O
thriller O
film O
directed O
and O
co O
written O
by O
Park B-PERSON
Chan I-PERSON
wook I-PERSON
A O
loose O
adaptation O
of O
the O
Japanese B-NORP
manga O
of O
the O
same O
name O
the O
film O
follows O
the O
story O
of O
Oh B-PERSON
Dae I-PERSON
su I-PERSON
who O
is O
imprisoned O
in O
a O
cell O
which O
resembles O
a O
hotel O
room O
for O
15 B-DATE
years I-DATE
without O
knowing O
the O
identity O
of O
his O
captor O
or O
his O
captor O
s O
motives O
When O
he O
is O
finally O
released O
Dae B-PERSON
su I-PERSON
finds O
himself O
still O
trapped O
in O
a O
web O
of O
conspiracy O
and O
violence O
His O
own O
quest O
for O
vengeance O
becomes O
tied O
in O
with O
romance O
when O
he O
falls O
in O
love O
with O
an O
attractive O
young O
sushi O
chef O
Mi B-PERSON
do I-PERSON
. O

Memento B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2000 B-DATE
American B-NORP
neo O
noir O
mystery O
thriller O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Christopher B-PERSON
Nolan I-PERSON
and O
produced O
by O
Suzanne B-PERSON
and O
Jennifer B-PERSON
Todd I-PERSON
The O
film O
s O
script O
was O
based O
on O
a O
pitch O
by O
Nolan B-PERSON
s O
brother O
Jonathan B-PERSON
who O
wrote O
the O
2001 B-DATE
story O
Memento B-WORK_OF_ART
Mori I-WORK_OF_ART
from O
the O
concept O
Guy B-PERSON
Pearce I-PERSON
stars O
as O
Leonard B-PERSON
Shelby I-PERSON
a O
man O
who O
suffers O
from O
anterograde O
amnesia O
resulting O
in O
short O
term O
memory O
loss O
and O
the O
inability O
to O
form O
new O
memories O
He O
is O
searching O
for O
the O
people O
who O
attacked O
him O
and O
killed O
his O
wife O
using O
an O
intricate O
system O
of O
Polaroid B-ORG
photographs O
and O
tattoos O
to O
track O
information O
he O
can O
not O
remember O
Carrie B-PERSON
Anne I-PERSON
Moss I-PERSON
and O
Joe B-PERSON
Pantoliano I-PERSON
co O
star O
. O

Princess B-WORK_OF_ART
Mononoke I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1997 B-DATE
Japanese B-NORP
animated O
epic O
historical O
fantasy O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Hayao B-PERSON
Miyazaki I-PERSON
animated O
by O
Studio B-ORG
Ghibli I-ORG
for O
Tokuma B-ORG
Shoten I-ORG
Nippon I-ORG
Television I-ORG
Network I-ORG
and O
Dentsu B-ORG
and O
distributed O
by O
Toho B-ORG
The O
film O
stars O
the O
voices O
of O
Yōji B-PERSON
Matsuda I-PERSON
Yuriko I-PERSON
Ishida I-PERSON
Yūko I-PERSON
Tanaka I-PERSON
Kaoru B-PERSON
Kobayashi I-PERSON
Masahiko B-PERSON
Nishimura I-PERSON
Tsunehiko B-PERSON
Kamijo I-PERSON
Akihiro B-PERSON
Miwa I-PERSON
Mitsuko B-PERSON
Mori I-PERSON
and O
Hisaya B-PERSON
Morishige I-PERSON
. O

Once B-WORK_OF_ART
Upon I-WORK_OF_ART
a I-WORK_OF_ART
Time I-WORK_OF_ART
in I-WORK_OF_ART
America I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1984 B-DATE
epic O
crime O
film O
co O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Italian B-NORP
filmmaker O
Sergio B-PERSON
Leone I-PERSON
and O
starring O
Robert B-PERSON
De I-PERSON
Niro I-PERSON
and O
James B-PERSON
Woods I-PERSON
The O
film O
is O
an O
Italian B-NORP
American B-NORP
venture O
produced O
by O
The B-ORG
Ladd I-ORG
Company I-ORG
Embassy O
International B-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
PSO B-ORG
Enterprises I-ORG
and O
Rafran B-ORG
Cinematografica I-ORG
and O
distributed O
by O
Warner B-ORG
Bros I-ORG
Based O
on O
Harry B-PERSON
Grey I-PERSON
s I-PERSON
novel O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Hoods I-WORK_OF_ART
it O
chronicles O
the O
lives O
of O
best O
friends O
David B-PERSON
Noodles I-PERSON
Aaronson I-PERSON
and O
Maximilian B-PERSON
Max I-PERSON
Bercovicz I-PERSON
as O
they O
lead O
a O
group O
of O
Jewish B-NORP
ghetto O
youths O
who O
rise O
to O
prominence O
as O
Jewish B-NORP
gangsters O
in O
New B-GPE
York I-GPE
City I-GPE
s I-GPE
world O
of O
organized O
crime O
The O
film O
explores O
themes O
of O
childhood O
friendships O
love O
lust O
greed O
betrayal O
loss O
broken O
relationships O
together O
with O
the O
rise O
of O
mobsters O
in O
American B-NORP
society O
. O

Raiders B-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Lost I-WORK_OF_ART
Ark I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1981 B-DATE
American B-NORP
action O
adventure O
film O
directed O
by O
Steven B-PERSON
Spielberg I-PERSON
with O
a O
screenplay O
by O
Lawrence B-PERSON
Kasdan I-PERSON
based O
on O
a O
story O
by O
George B-PERSON
Lucas I-PERSON
and O
Philip B-PERSON
Kaufman I-PERSON
It O
stars O
Harrison B-PERSON
Ford I-PERSON
Karen B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
Paul B-PERSON
Freeman I-PERSON
Ronald B-PERSON
Lacey I-PERSON
John B-PERSON
Rhys I-PERSON
Davies I-PERSON
and O
Denholm B-PERSON
Elliott I-PERSON
Ford I-PERSON
portrays O
Indiana B-PERSON
Jones I-PERSON
a O
globe O
trotting O
archaeologist O
vying O
with O
Nazi B-NORP
German B-NORP
forces O
in O
1936 B-DATE
to O
recover O
the O
long O
lost O
Ark O
of O
the O
Covenant O
a O
relic O
said O
to O
make O
an O
army O
invincible O
Teaming O
up O
with O
his O
tough O
former O
lover O
Marion B-PERSON
Ravenwood I-PERSON
Allen B-PERSON
Jones I-PERSON
races O
to O
stop O
rival O
archaeologist O
Dr O
René B-PERSON
Belloq I-PERSON
Freeman I-PERSON
from O
guiding O
the O
Nazis B-NORP
to O
the O
Ark B-FAC
and O
its O
power O
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Shining I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1980 B-DATE
psychological O
horror O
film O
produced O
and O
directed O
by O
Stanley B-PERSON
Kubrick I-PERSON
and O
co O
written O
with O
novelist O
Diane B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
The O
film O
is O
based O
on O
Stephen B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
s I-PERSON
1977 B-DATE
novel O
of O
the O
same O
name O
and O
stars O
Jack B-PERSON
Nicholson I-PERSON
Shelley B-PERSON
Duvall B-PERSON
Scatman I-PERSON
Crothers I-PERSON
and O
Danny B-PERSON
Lloyd I-PERSON
. O

Apocalypse B-WORK_OF_ART
Now I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1979 B-DATE
American B-NORP
epic O
psychological O
war O
film O
directed O
and O
produced O
by O
Francis B-PERSON
Ford I-PERSON
Coppola I-PERSON
It O
stars O
Marlon B-PERSON
Brando I-PERSON
Robert B-PERSON
Duvall I-PERSON
Martin B-PERSON
Sheen I-PERSON
Frederic B-PERSON
Forrest I-PERSON
Albert B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
Sam B-PERSON
Bottoms I-PERSON
Laurence B-PERSON
Fishburne I-PERSON
and O
Dennis B-PERSON
Hopper I-PERSON
The O
screenplay O
co O
written O
by O
Coppola B-PERSON
and O
John B-PERSON
Milius I-PERSON
with O
narration O
written O
by O
Michael B-PERSON
Herr I-PERSON
is O
loosely O
based O
on O
the O
1899 B-DATE
novella O
Heart B-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
Darkness I-WORK_OF_ART
by O
Joseph B-PERSON
Conrad I-PERSON
with O
the O
setting O
changed O
from O
late B-DATE
19th I-DATE
century I-DATE
Congo B-GPE
to O
the B-EVENT
Vietnam I-EVENT
War I-EVENT
The O
film O
follows O
a O
river O
journey O
from O
South B-GPE
Vietnam I-GPE
into O
Cambodia B-GPE
undertaken O
by O
Captain O
Benjamin B-PERSON
L I-PERSON
Willard I-PERSON
Sheen I-PERSON
who O
is O
on O
a O
secret O
mission O
to O
assassinate O
Colonel O
Kurtz B-PERSON
Brando I-PERSON
a O
renegade O
Army B-ORG
Special I-ORG
Forces I-ORG
officer O
accused O
of O
murder O
and O
who O
is O
presumed O
insane O
. O

Alien B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1979 B-DATE
science O
fiction O
horror O
film O
directed O
by O
Ridley B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
Dan B-PERSON
O I-PERSON
Bannon I-PERSON
Based O
on O
a O
story O
by O
O B-PERSON
Bannon I-PERSON
and O
Ronald B-PERSON
Shusett I-PERSON
it O
follows O
the O
crew O
of O
the O
commercial O
space O
tug O
Nostromo B-PRODUCT
who O
encounter O
the O
eponymous O
Alien B-PRODUCT
an O
aggressive O
and O
deadly O
extraterrestrial O
set O
loose O
on O
the O
ship O
The O
film O
stars O
Tom B-PERSON
Skerritt I-PERSON
Sigourney B-PERSON
Weaver I-PERSON
Veronica B-PERSON
Cartwright I-PERSON
Harry B-PERSON
Dean I-PERSON
Stanton I-PERSON
John B-PERSON
Hurt I-PERSON
Ian B-PERSON
Holm I-PERSON
and O
Yaphet B-PERSON
Kotto I-PERSON
It O
was O
produced O
by O
Gordon B-PERSON
Carroll I-PERSON
David B-PERSON
Giler I-PERSON
and O
Walter B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
through O
their O
company O
Brandywine B-ORG
Productions I-ORG
and O
was O
distributed O
by O
20th B-ORG
Century I-ORG
Fox I-ORG
Giler B-PERSON
and O
Hill B-PERSON
revised O
and O
made O
additions O
to O
the O
script O
Shusett B-PERSON
was O
executive O
producer O
The O
Alien O
and O
its O
accompanying O
artifacts O
were O
designed O
by O
the O
Swiss B-NORP
artist O
H B-PERSON
R I-PERSON
Giger I-PERSON
while O
concept O
artists O
Ron B-PERSON
Cobb I-PERSON
and O
Chris B-PERSON
Foss I-PERSON
designed O
the O
more O
human O
settings O
. O

Dr B-WORK_OF_ART
Strangelove I-WORK_OF_ART
or O
How O
I O
Learned O
to O
Stop O
Worrying O
and O
Love O
the O
Bomb O
more O
commonly O
known O
simply O
as O
Dr B-WORK_OF_ART
Strangelove I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1964 B-DATE
black O
comedy O
film O
that O
satirizes O
the O
Cold B-EVENT
War I-EVENT
fears O
of O
a O
nuclear O
conflict O
between O
the B-GPE
Soviet I-GPE
Union I-GPE
and O
the B-GPE
United I-GPE
States I-GPE
The O
film O
was O
directed O
produced O
and O
co O
written O
by O
Stanley B-PERSON
Kubrick I-PERSON
and O
stars O
Peter B-PERSON
Sellers I-PERSON
George B-PERSON
C I-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
Sterling I-PERSON
Hayden I-PERSON
and O
Slim B-PERSON
Pickens I-PERSON
It O
was O
made O
in O
the B-GPE
United I-GPE
Kingdom I-GPE
and O
is O
loosely O
based O
on O
Peter B-PERSON
George I-PERSON
s I-PERSON
thriller O
novel O
Red B-WORK_OF_ART
Alert I-WORK_OF_ART
1958 B-DATE
. O

Witness B-WORK_OF_ART
for I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Prosecution I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1957 B-DATE
American B-NORP
film O
co O
adapted O
and O
directed O
by O
Billy B-PERSON
Wilder I-PERSON
and O
starring O
Tyrone B-PERSON
Power I-PERSON
Marlene B-PERSON
Dietrich I-PERSON
Charles B-PERSON
Laughton I-PERSON
and O
Elsa B-PERSON
Lanchester I-PERSON
The O
film O
which O
has O
film O
noir O
elements O
depicts O
an O
English B-NORP
courtroom O
drama O
Set O
in O
the B-FAC
Old I-FAC
Bailey I-FAC
in O
London B-GPE
the O
picture O
is O
based O
on O
the O
1953 B-DATE
play O
of O
the O
same O
name O
by O
Agatha B-PERSON
Christie I-PERSON
and O
deals O
with O
the O
trial O
of O
a O
man O
accused O
of O
murder O
The O
first B-ORDINAL
film O
adaptation O
of O
Christie B-PERSON
s O
story O
Witness B-WORK_OF_ART
for I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Prosecution I-WORK_OF_ART
was O
adapted O
for O
the O
screen O
by O
Larry B-PERSON
Marcus I-PERSON
Harry I-PERSON
Kurnitz I-PERSON
and O
Wilder B-PERSON
The O
film O
received O
positive O
reviews O
and O
six B-CARDINAL
Academy B-WORK_OF_ART
Award I-WORK_OF_ART
nominations O
. O

Paths B-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
Glory I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1957 B-DATE
American B-NORP
anti O
war O
film O
co O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Stanley B-PERSON
Kubrick I-PERSON
based O
on O
the O
novel O
of O
the O
same O
name O
by O
Humphrey B-PERSON
Cobb I-PERSON
Set O
during O
World B-EVENT
War I-EVENT
I I-EVENT
the O
film O
stars O
Kirk B-PERSON
Douglas I-PERSON
as O
Colonel O
Dax B-PERSON
the O
commanding O
officer O
of O
French B-NORP
soldiers O
who O
refuse O
to O
continue O
a O
suicidal O
attack O
after O
which O
Dax B-PERSON
attempts O
to O
defend O
them O
against O
charges O
of O
cowardice O
in O
a O
court O
martial O
. O

Rear B-WORK_OF_ART
Window I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1954 B-DATE
American B-NORP
mystery O
thriller O
film O
directed O
by O
Alfred B-PERSON
Hitchcock I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
John B-PERSON
Michael I-PERSON
Hayes I-PERSON
based O
on O
Cornell B-PERSON
Woolrich I-PERSON
s I-PERSON
1942 B-DATE
short O
story O
It B-WORK_OF_ART
Had I-WORK_OF_ART
to I-WORK_OF_ART
Be I-WORK_OF_ART
Murder I-WORK_OF_ART
Originally O
released O
by O
Paramount B-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
the O
film O
stars O
James B-PERSON
Stewart I-PERSON
Grace I-PERSON
Kelly I-PERSON
Wendell B-PERSON
Corey B-PERSON
Thelma I-PERSON
Ritter I-PERSON
and O
Raymond B-PERSON
Burr I-PERSON
It O
was O
screened O
at O
the O
1954 B-DATE
Venice B-EVENT
Film I-EVENT
Festival I-EVENT
. O

Sunset B-FAC
Boulevard I-FAC
is O
a O
boulevard O
in O
the O
central O
and O
western O
part O
of O
Los B-GPE
Angeles I-GPE
California B-GPE
that O
stretches O
from O
the B-FAC
Pacific I-FAC
Coast I-FAC
Highway I-FAC
in O
Pacific B-LOC
Palisades I-LOC
east O
to O
Figueroa B-FAC
Street I-FAC
in O
Downtown B-GPE
Los I-GPE
Angeles I-GPE
It O
is O
a O
major O
thoroughfare O
in O
the O
cities O
of O
Beverly B-GPE
Hills I-GPE
and O
West B-GPE
Hollywood I-GPE
as O
well O
as O
several O
districts O
in O
Los B-GPE
Angeles I-GPE
. O

The B-WORK_OF_ART
Great I-WORK_OF_ART
Dictator I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1940 B-DATE
American B-NORP
satirical O
comedy O
drama O
film O
written O
directed O
produced O
scored O
by O
and O
starring O
British B-NORP
comedian O
Charlie B-PERSON
Chaplin I-PERSON
following O
the O
tradition O
of O
many O
of O
his O
other O
films O
Having O
been O
the O
only O
Hollywood B-GPE
filmmaker O
to O
continue O
to O
make O
silent O
films O
well O
into O
the O
period O
of O
sound O
films O
Chaplin B-PERSON
made O
this O
his O
first B-ORDINAL
true O
sound O
film O
. O

1917 B-DATE
MCMXVII B-DATE
was O
a O
common O
year O
starting O
on O
Monday B-DATE
of I-DATE
the I-DATE
Gregorian I-DATE
calendar I-DATE
and O
a O
common O
year O
starting O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
of I-DATE
the I-DATE
Julian I-DATE
calendar I-DATE
the I-DATE
1917th I-DATE
year I-DATE
of I-DATE
the I-DATE
Common I-DATE
Era I-DATE
CE I-DATE
and O
Anno B-DATE
Domini I-DATE
AD I-DATE
designations O
the B-DATE
917th I-DATE
year I-DATE
of I-DATE
the I-DATE
2nd I-DATE
millennium I-DATE
the B-DATE
17th I-DATE
year I-DATE
of I-DATE
the I-DATE
20th I-DATE
century I-DATE
and O
the B-DATE
8th I-DATE
year I-DATE
of I-DATE
the I-DATE
1910s I-DATE
decade I-DATE
As O
of O
the B-DATE
start I-DATE
of I-DATE
1917 I-DATE
the O
Gregorian O
calendar O
was O
13 B-DATE
days I-DATE
ahead O
of O
the O
Julian O
calendar O
which O
remained O
in O
localized O
use O
until O
1923 B-DATE
. O

Tumbbad B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2018 B-DATE
Indian B-NORP
Hindi B-LANGUAGE
language O
period O
drama O
supernatural O
horror O
film O
directed O
by O
Rahi B-PERSON
Anil I-PERSON
Barve I-PERSON
with O
Anand B-PERSON
Gandhi I-PERSON
serving O
as O
the O
creative O
director O
and O
Adesh B-PERSON
Prasad I-PERSON
serving O
as O
the O
co O
director O
Written O
by O
Mitesh B-PERSON
Shah I-PERSON
Prasad I-PERSON
Barve I-PERSON
and O
Gandhi B-PERSON
the O
film O
was O
produced O
by O
Sohum B-PERSON
Shah I-PERSON
Aanand I-PERSON
L I-PERSON
Rai I-PERSON
Mukesh I-PERSON
Shah I-PERSON
and O
Amita B-PERSON
Shah I-PERSON
Starring O
Sohum B-PERSON
Shah I-PERSON
in O
the O
lead O
role O
it O
follows O
the O
story O
of O
a O
man O
s O
search O
for O
a O
hidden O
treasure O
in O
the O
20th B-DATE
century I-DATE
British B-NORP
India O
village O
of O
Tumbbad B-GPE
Maharashtra B-GPE
. O

ndhadhun B-WORK_OF_ART
transl I-WORK_OF_ART
Blindly I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2018 B-DATE
Indian B-NORP
Hindi B-LANGUAGE
language O
black O
comedy O
crime O
thriller O
film O
co O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Sriram B-PERSON
Raghavan I-PERSON
produced O
by O
Matchbox B-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
and O
distributed O
by O
Viacom18 B-ORG
Motion I-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
The O
film O
stars O
Tabu B-PERSON
Ayushmann I-PERSON
Khurrana I-PERSON
and O
Radhika B-PERSON
Apte I-PERSON
and O
tells O
the O
story O
of O
a O
blind O
piano O
player O
who O
unwittingly O
becomes O
embroiled O
in O
the O
murder O
of O
a O
retired O
actor O
. O

Drishyam B-WORK_OF_ART
transl I-WORK_OF_ART
Visual I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2013 B-DATE
Indian B-NORP
Malayalam I-NORP
language I-NORP
crime I-NORP
thriller I-NORP
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Jeethu B-PERSON
Joseph I-PERSON
It O
stars O
Mohanlal B-PERSON
and O
Meena B-PERSON
with O
Ansiba B-PERSON
Hassan I-PERSON
Esther B-PERSON
Anil I-PERSON
Kalabhavan I-PERSON
Shajohn B-PERSON
Asha B-PERSON
Sharath I-PERSON
Siddique B-PERSON
Roshan I-PERSON
Basheer I-PERSON
and O
Neeraj B-PERSON
Madhav I-PERSON
in O
supporting O
roles O
The O
film O
was O
produced O
by O
Antony B-PERSON
Perumbavoor I-PERSON
for O
Aashirvad B-ORG
Cinemas I-ORG
It O
follows O
the O
struggle O
of O
Georgekutty B-PERSON
and O
his O
family O
who O
come O
under O
suspicion O
when O
Varun B-PERSON
Prabhakar I-PERSON
the O
son O
of O
the O
Inspector O
General O
of O
Police O
goes O
missing O
. O

The O
Hunt B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2012 B-DATE
Danish B-NORP
drama O
film O
directed O
by O
Thomas B-PERSON
Vinterberg I-PERSON
and O
starring O
Mads B-PERSON
Mikkelsen I-PERSON
It O
is O
set O
in O
a O
small O
Danish B-NORP
village O
around O
Christmas B-DATE
and O
follows O
a O
man O
who O
becomes O
the O
target O
of O
mass O
hysteria O
after O
being O
wrongly O
accused O
of O
sexually O
abusing O
a O
child O
in O
his O
kindergarten O
class O
. O

A B-WORK_OF_ART
Separation I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2011 B-DATE
Iranian B-NORP
drama O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Asghar B-PERSON
Farhadi I-PERSON
starring O
Leila B-PERSON
Hatami I-PERSON
Peyman I-PERSON
Moaadi I-PERSON
Shahab I-PERSON
Hosseini I-PERSON
Sareh I-PERSON
Bayat I-PERSON
and O
Sarina B-PERSON
Farhadi I-PERSON
It O
focuses O
on O
an O
Iranian B-NORP
middle O
class O
couple O
who O
separate O
the O
disappointment O
and O
desperation O
suffered O
by O
their O
daughter O
due O
to O
the O
egotistical O
disputes O
and O
separation O
of O
her O
parents O
and O
the O
conflicts O
that O
arise O
when O
the O
husband O
hires O
a O
lower O
class O
caregiver O
for O
his O
elderly O
father O
who O
suffers O
from O
Alzheimer O
s O
disease O
. O

Miracle B-WORK_OF_ART
in I-WORK_OF_ART
Cell I-WORK_OF_ART
No I-WORK_OF_ART
7 I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2013 B-DATE
South B-NORP
Korean I-NORP
comedy O
drama O
film O
starring O
Ryu B-PERSON
Seung I-PERSON
ryong I-PERSON
Kal I-PERSON
So I-PERSON
won I-PERSON
and O
Park B-PERSON
Shin I-PERSON
hye I-PERSON
The O
film O
is O
about O
a O
mentally O
challenged O
man O
wrongfully O
imprisoned O
for O
murder O
who O
builds O
friendships O
with O
the O
hardened O
criminals O
in O
his O
cell O
who O
in O
return O
help O
him O
see O
his O
daughter O
again O
by O
smuggling O
her O
into O
the O
prison O
. O

My B-WORK_OF_ART
Father I-WORK_OF_ART
and I-WORK_OF_ART
My I-WORK_OF_ART
Son I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2005 B-DATE
Turkish B-NORP
drama O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
a B-PERSON
an I-PERSON
Irmak I-PERSON
about O
a O
family O
torn O
apart O
by O
the O
1980 B-DATE
Turkish B-NORP
coup O
d O
état O
The O
film O
which O
went O
on O
nationwide O
release O
on O
18 B-DATE
November I-DATE
2005 I-DATE
became O
one B-CARDINAL
of O
the O
highest O
grossing O
Turkish B-NORP
films O
in O
history O
. O

Inglourious B-WORK_OF_ART
Basterds I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2009 B-DATE
war O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Quentin B-PERSON
Tarantino I-PERSON
and O
starring O
Brad B-PERSON
Pitt I-PERSON
Christoph B-PERSON
Waltz I-PERSON
Michael B-PERSON
Fassbender I-PERSON
Eli B-PERSON
Roth I-PERSON
Diane B-PERSON
Kruger I-PERSON
Daniel B-PERSON
Brühl I-PERSON
Til B-PERSON
Schweiger I-PERSON
and O
Mélanie B-PERSON
Laurent I-PERSON
The O
film O
tells O
an O
alternate O
history O
story O
of O
two B-CARDINAL
plots O
to O
assassinate O
Nazi O
Germany B-GPE
s O
leadership O
one O
planned O
by O
Shosanna B-PERSON
Dreyfus I-PERSON
Laurent I-PERSON
a O
young O
French B-NORP
Jewish B-NORP
cinema O
proprietor O
and O
the O
other O
by O
the O
British B-NORP
but O
ultimately O
conducted O
solely O
by O
a O
team O
of O
Jewish B-NORP
American B-NORP
soldiers O
led O
by O
First O
Lieutenant O
Aldo B-PERSON
Raine I-PERSON
Pitt O
Christoph B-PERSON
Waltz I-PERSON
co O
stars O
as O
Hans B-PERSON
Landa I-PERSON
an O
SS B-ORG
colonel O
in O
charge O
of O
tracking O
down O
Raine B-PERSON
s O
group O
The O
title O
was O
inspired O
by O
Italian B-NORP
director O
Enzo B-PERSON
G I-PERSON
Castellari I-PERSON
s O
Euro B-EVENT
War I-EVENT
film O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
Inglorious I-WORK_OF_ART
Bastards I-WORK_OF_ART
1978 I-WORK_OF_ART
though O
Tarantino B-PERSON
s O
film O
is O
not O
a O
remake O
of O
it O
. O

Eternal B-WORK_OF_ART
Sunshine I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
the I-WORK_OF_ART
Spotless I-WORK_OF_ART
Mind I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2004 B-DATE
American B-NORP
romantic O
science O
fiction O
drama O
film O
written O
by O
Charlie B-PERSON
Kaufman I-PERSON
directed O
by O
Michel B-PERSON
Gondry I-PERSON
and O
starring O
Jim B-PERSON
Carrey I-PERSON
and O
Kate B-PERSON
Winslet I-PERSON
Pierre B-PERSON
Bismuth I-PERSON
created O
the O
story O
with O
Kaufman B-PERSON
and O
Gondry B-PERSON
The O
film O
features O
an O
ensemble O
supporting O
cast O
that O
includes O
Kirsten B-PERSON
Dunst I-PERSON
Mark B-PERSON
Ruffalo I-PERSON
Elijah B-PERSON
Wood I-PERSON
and O
Tom B-PERSON
Wilkinson I-PERSON
The O
title O
of O
the O
film O
is O
a O
quotation O
from O
the O
1717 B-DATE
poem O
Eloisa B-WORK_OF_ART
to I-WORK_OF_ART
Abelard I-WORK_OF_ART
by O
Alexander B-PERSON
Pope I-PERSON
. O

Amélie B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2001 B-DATE
French B-LANGUAGE
language O
romantic O
comedy O
film O
directed O
by O
Jean B-PERSON
Pierre I-PERSON
Jeunet I-PERSON
Written O
by O
Jeunet B-PERSON
with O
Guillaume B-PERSON
Laurant I-PERSON
the O
film O
is O
a O
whimsical O
depiction O
of O
contemporary O
Parisian B-NORP
life O
set O
in O
Montmartre B-GPE
It O
tells O
the O
story O
of O
a O
shy O
waitress O
played O
by O
Audrey B-PERSON
Tautou I-PERSON
who O
decides O
to O
change O
the O
lives O
of O
those O
around O
her O
for O
the O
better O
while O
dealing O
with O
her O
own O
isolation O
The O
film O
also O
features O
an O
ensemble O
cast O
of O
supporting O
roles O
including O
Mathieu B-PERSON
Kassovitz I-PERSON
Rufus I-PERSON
Lorella I-PERSON
Cravotta I-PERSON
Serge B-PERSON
Merlin I-PERSON
Jamel I-PERSON
Debbouze I-PERSON
Claire B-PERSON
Maurier I-PERSON
Clotilde B-PERSON
Mollet I-PERSON
Isabelle B-PERSON
Nanty I-PERSON
Dominique B-PERSON
Pinon I-PERSON
Artus I-PERSON
de I-PERSON
Penguern I-PERSON
Yolande B-PERSON
Moreau I-PERSON
Urbain I-PERSON
Cancelier I-PERSON
and O
Maurice B-PERSON
Bénichou I-PERSON
. O

Snatch B-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2000 B-DATE
crime O
comedy O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Guy B-PERSON
Ritchie I-PERSON
featuring O
an O
ensemble O
cast O
Set O
in O
the O
London B-GPE
criminal O
underworld O
the O
film O
contains O
two B-CARDINAL
intertwined O
plots O
one B-CARDINAL
dealing O
with O
the O
search O
for O
a O
stolen O
diamond O
the O
other O
with O
a O
small O
time O
boxing O
promoter O
who O
finds O
himself O
under O
the O
thumb O
of O
a O
ruthless O
gangster O
who O
is O
ready O
and O
willing O
to O
have O
his O
subordinates O
carry O
out O
severe O
and O
sadistic O
acts O
of O
violence O
. O

Requiem B-WORK_OF_ART
for I-WORK_OF_ART
a I-WORK_OF_ART
Dream I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
2000 B-DATE
American B-NORP
psychological O
drama O
film O
directed O
by O
Darren B-PERSON
Aronofsky I-PERSON
and O
starring O
Ellen B-PERSON
Burstyn I-PERSON
Jared B-PERSON
Leto I-PERSON
Jennifer B-PERSON
Connelly I-PERSON
and O
Marlon B-PERSON
Wayans I-PERSON
It O
is O
based O
on O
the O
1978 B-DATE
novel O
of O
the O
same O
name O
by O
Hubert B-PERSON
Selby I-PERSON
Jr I-PERSON
with O
whom O
Aronofsky B-PERSON
wrote O
the O
screenplay O
The O
film O
depicts O
four B-CARDINAL
characters O
affected O
by O
drug O
addiction O
and O
how O
it O
alters O
their O
physical O
and O
emotional O
states O
Their O
addictions O
cause O
them O
to O
become O
imprisoned O
in O
a O
world O
of O
delusion O
and O
desperation O
As O
the O
film O
progresses O
each O
character O
deteriorates O
and O
their O
reality O
is O
overtaken O
by O
delusion O
resulting O
in O
catastrophe O
. O

American B-WORK_OF_ART
Beauty I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1999 B-DATE
American B-NORP
black O
comedy O
drama O
film O
written O
by O
Alan B-PERSON
Ball I-PERSON
and O
directed O
by O
Sam B-PERSON
Mendes I-PERSON
Kevin B-PERSON
Spacey I-PERSON
stars O
as O
Lester B-PERSON
Burnham I-PERSON
an O
advertising O
executive O
who O
has O
a O
midlife O
crisis O
when O
he O
becomes O
infatuated O
with O
his O
teenage O
daughter O
s O
best O
friend O
played O
by O
Mena B-PERSON
Suvari I-PERSON
Annette B-PERSON
Bening I-PERSON
stars O
as O
Lester B-PERSON
s O
materialistic O
wife O
Carolyn B-PERSON
and O
Thora B-PERSON
Birch I-PERSON
plays O
their O
insecure O
daughter O
Jane B-PERSON
Wes I-PERSON
Bentley I-PERSON
Chris B-PERSON
Cooper I-PERSON
and O
Allison B-PERSON
Janney I-PERSON
also O
feature O
Academics B-ORG
have O
described O
the O
film O
as O
satirizing O
how O
beauty O
and O
personal O
satisfaction O
are O
perceived O
by O
the O
American B-NORP
middle O
class O
further O
analysis O
has O
focused O
on O
the O
film O
s O
explorations O
of O
romantic O
and O
paternal O
love O
sexuality O
materialism O
self O
liberation O
and O
redemption O
. O

Good B-WORK_OF_ART
Will I-WORK_OF_ART
Hunting I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1997 B-DATE
American B-NORP
psychological O
drama O
film O
directed O
by O
Gus B-PERSON
Van I-PERSON
Sant I-PERSON
and O
starring O
Robin B-PERSON
Williams I-PERSON
Matt B-PERSON
Damon I-PERSON
Ben B-PERSON
Affleck I-PERSON
Minnie B-PERSON
Driver I-PERSON
and O
Stellan B-PERSON
Skarsg I-PERSON
rd O
Written O
by O
Affleck B-PERSON
and O
Damon B-PERSON
the O
film O
follows O
20 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
South B-LOC
Boston I-LOC
janitor O
Will B-PERSON
Hunting I-PERSON
Damon O
an O
unrecognized O
genius O
who O
as O
part O
of O
a O
deferred O
prosecution O
agreement O
after O
assaulting O
a O
police O
officer O
becomes O
a O
patient O
of O
a O
therapist O
Williams B-PERSON
and O
studies O
advanced O
mathematics O
with O
a O
renowned O
professor O
Skarsg B-PERSON
rd O
Through O
his O
therapy O
sessions O
Will B-PERSON
re O
evaluates O
his O
relationships O
with O
his O
best O
friend O
Affleck B-PERSON
his O
girlfriend O
Driver B-PERSON
and O
himself O
facing O
the O
significant O
task O
of O
confronting O
his O
past O
and O
thinking O
about O
his O
future O
. O

Children B-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
Heaven I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1997 B-DATE
Iranian B-NORP
family O
drama O
film O
written O
and O
directed O
by O
Majid B-PERSON
Majidi I-PERSON
It O
deals O
with O
a O
brother O
and O
sister O
and O
their O
adventures O
over O
a O
lost O
pair O
of O
shoes O
It O
was O
nominated O
for O
the B-WORK_OF_ART
Academy I-WORK_OF_ART
Award I-WORK_OF_ART
for O
Best B-WORK_OF_ART
Foreign I-WORK_OF_ART
Language I-WORK_OF_ART
Film I-WORK_OF_ART
in O
1998 B-DATE
. O

Toy B-WORK_OF_ART
Story I-WORK_OF_ART
is O
a O
1995 B-DATE
American B-NORP
computer O
animated O
comedy O
film O
produced O
by O
Pixar B-ORG
Animation I-ORG
Studios I-ORG
and O
released O
by O
Walt B-ORG
Disney I-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
The O
first B-ORDINAL
installment O
in O
the O
Toy B-WORK_OF_ART
Story I-WORK_OF_ART
franchise O
it O
was O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
entirely O
computer O
animated O
feature O
film O
as O
well O
as O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
feature O
film O
from O
Pixar B-ORG
The O
film O
was O
directed O
by O
John B-PERSON
Lasseter I-PERSON
and O
written O
by O
Joss B-PERSON
Whedon I-PERSON
Andrew B-PERSON
Stanton I-PERSON
Joel B-PERSON
Cohen I-PERSON
and O
Alec B-PERSON
Sokolow I-PERSON
from O
a O
story O
by O
Lasseter B-PERSON
Stanton I-PERSON
Pete B-PERSON
Docter I-PERSON
and O
Joe B-PERSON
Ranft I-PERSON
The O
film O
features O
music O
by O
Randy B-PERSON
Newman I-PERSON
was O
produced O
by O
Bonnie B-PERSON
Arnold I-PERSON
and O
Ralph B-PERSON
Guggenheim I-PERSON
and O
was O
executive O
produced O
by O
Steve B-PERSON
Jobs I-PERSON
and O
Edwin B-PERSON
Catmull I-PERSON
The O
film O
features O
the O
voices O
of O
Tom B-PERSON
Hanks I-PERSON
Tim B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
Don B-PERSON
Rickles I-PERSON
Wallace B-PERSON
Shawn B-PERSON
John B-PERSON
Ratzenberger I-PERSON
Jim B-PERSON
Varney I-PERSON
Annie B-PERSON
Potts I-PERSON
R B-PERSON
Lee B-PERSON
Ermey I-PERSON
John B-PERSON
Morris I-PERSON
Laurie B-PERSON
Metcalf I-PERSON
and O
Erik B-PERSON
von I-PERSON
Detten I-PERSON
Taking O
place O
in O
a O
world O
where O
toys O
come O
to O
life O
when O
humans O
are O
not O
present O
the O
plot O
focuses O
on O
the O
relationship O
between O
an O
old O
fashioned O
pull O
string O
cowboy O
doll O
named O
Woody B-PERSON
and O
a O
modern O
astronaut O
action O
figure O
Buzz B-PERSON
Lightyear I-PERSON
as O
they O
evolve O
from O
rivals O
competing O
for O
the O
affections O
of O
their O
owner O
Andy B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
to O
friends O
who O
work O
together O
to O
be O
reunited O
with O
Andy B-PERSON
after O
being O
separated O
from O
him O
. O
